This website is for adults only

This website contains age-restricted materials including nudity and explicit depictions of sexual activity. By entering, you affirm that you are at least 18 years of age or the age of majority in the jurisdiction you are accessing the website from and you consent to viewing sexually explicit content.

I am 18 or older - Enter I am under 18 - Exit

Our [parental controls page](https://www.asacp.org/index.html?content=parental_guidelines) explains how you can easily block access to this site.

© Youporn 2024 [](https://help.pornhub.com/hc/en-us/articles/4419885579795)

Your Cookies, Your Choice

We use cookies and similar technologies that are necessary to run our Website (essential cookies). We use Analytics, Functionality and Targeting cookies to analyse our Website’s traffic, optimize your experience, personalize content and serve targeted advertisements. You can switch off cookies at any time by visiting the Manage Cookies option at the footer of the page. Learn more in our [Cookie Notice](https://www.youporn.com/information/cookie-notice). For more information about how we process your personal data, please refer to our [Privacy Notice](https://www.youporn.com/information/#privacy).

Please make a selection

Accept all cookies Accept only essential cookies Manage Cookies

Some features may not be available with your selection. For better browsing experience, select ' ['Accept All Cookies'](#) '.

Manage Cookies

manage cookies
--------------

Back

#### Essential

 always active

These cookies are necessary for the Website to function and cannot be switched off in our systems as they enable core website functionality. They are used to carry out the transmission of a communication, provide you with the requested services or are set in response to actions made by you, such as setting your privacy preferences, logging in or filling in forms. You can set your browser to block these cookies, but that may cause some parts of the Website to not work properly.

#### Functional

These cookies are set to implement additional functionalities and/or to enhance features and website performance, improving your experience on the Website. This type of cookies allows us to recognize you when you return to the Website and to remember, for example, your choice of language and your preferences such as your region.

#### Analytics

These cookies allow us to recognize and count the number of users and to see how you use and explore the Website. For example, they allow us to carry out statistical analysis of page use, interactions, and paths you take through the Website to improve its performance. We use Google as a service provider to collect and analyse information about how you use the Website, including by collecting website activity data through first-party cookies set by our domains, and third-party cookies set by Google.

#### Targeting/Advertising

These cookies enable us to make the Website more relevant to your interests and to help us serve ads that might be of interest to you. We and our advertising partners set these cookies to provide behavioural advertising and define the number of ads that will be displayed to you. If you choose to disable this type of cookies, you will still see advertisements, but they will be less relevant and will not be tailored to your interests.

Accept all cookies Accept only essential cookies Save and close

#### Recent Searches

#### Trending Searches

#### Recommended Categories For You

#### Recommended Pornstars For You

[Frank Taylor

Pornstar](https://www.youporn.com/pornstar/frank-taylor/)

[Liana

Pornstar](https://www.youporn.com/pornstar/liana/)

[Dora Venter

Pornstar](https://www.youporn.com/pornstar/dora-venter/)

[Brittany Blaze

Pornstar](https://www.youporn.com/pornstar/brittany-blaze/)

[Simone Valentino

Pornstar](https://www.youporn.com/pornstar/simone-valentino/)

[Hercules

Pornstar](https://www.youporn.com/pornstar/hercules/)

[Johnny Rey

Pornstar](https://www.youporn.com/gay/pornstar/johnny-rey/)

#### Recommended Channels For You

#### All videos

* Personalized Recommendations 

* English

* Back

    Categories
    
    Top Trending & Most Popular
    
    ### Top Trending Categories

    ### Most Popular Categories
    
    [
    
    Big Tits](https://www.youporn.com/category/bigtits/)[
    
    Blowjob](https://www.youporn.com/category/blowjob/)[
    
    Asian](https://www.youporn.com/category/asian/)[
    
    Public](https://www.youporn.com/category/public/)[
    
    Ebony](https://www.youporn.com/category/ebony/)[
    
    Fetish](https://www.youporn.com/category/fetish/)

    Quick Links
    -----------

    Top Trending Pornstars
    ----------------------
    
    Recommended Pornstars For You
    -----------------------------

ADBLOCK DETECTED!

[Looks like you've enabled Adblock. Some features may break or not appear entirely. Please try disabling Adblock,](https://www.youpornpremium.com/premium_signup?type=AdBlock) [contact Adblock support to fix the issue](https://help.getadblock.com/support/tickets/new)

Terms Of Service
================

Last Modified: July 15, 2024

Acceptance of the Terms of Service

By accessing, using or visiting [https://www.youporn.com/](https://www.youporn.com/) (“**we**”, “**us**”, “**our**” or this “**Website**”), any of its Content, functionalities and services, you signify your agreement to these Terms of Service including policies and related guidelines (for instance, Child Sexual Abuse Material Policy and Non-Consensual Content Policy) (collectively “**Terms of Service**”), and our [Privacy Notice](https://www.youporn.com/information/#privacy) and incorporated herein by reference.

You may terminate these Terms of Service at any time by deleting your account and refraining from further use of our services.

These Terms of Service apply to all users, registered or unregistered, including Content Partners, and Models who may also be contributors of content, of this Website (collectively "**you**", "**User**" or "**Users**" as the context requires), whether accessed via computer, mobile device, or other technology, manner, or means.

“**Content**” includes the text, software, scripts, graphics, photos, sounds, music, videos, audiovisual combinations, interactive features, textual content, and other materials you may view, upload, publish, submit, make available, display, communicate or post on this Website.

“**Content Partners**” means users of this Website who have joined the [Pornhub Content Partner Program](https://www.pornhub.com/partners/cpp) and who may use their Pornhub Content Partner Program account to access this Website as a registered Content Partner.

“**Models**” means users of this Website who have joined our [Pornhub Model Partner Program](https://www.pornhub.com/partners/models) and who may use their Pornhub Model Partner Program account to access this Website as a registered Model and are subject to its terms and this Terms of Service.

If you do not agree to any of these Terms of Service or our [Privacy Notice](https://www.youporn.com/information/#privacy), please do not access or use this Website.

You consent to entering these Terms of Service electronically, and to storage of records related to these Terms of Service in electronic form.

Back to Top

Ability to Accept Terms of Service

You affirm that:

* You are at least eighteen (18) years of age or the age of majority in the jurisdiction you are accessing and/or using this Website from and are fully able and competent to enter into the terms, conditions, obligations, affirmations, representations, and warranties set forth in these Terms of Service, and to abide by and comply with these Terms of Service. **If you are under eighteen (18) years of age or the applicable age of majority, please do not use this Website.**
* You also represent that the jurisdiction from which you access this Website does not prohibit the receiving or viewing of sexually explicit Content.

Whether you are a registered or unregistered User, we may require that you provide us and/or our third-party age verification service providers with information which will help us determine that you are over the age of majority required to have access to this Website and to view its Contents. For more information on how this information is processed, please review our [Privacy Notice](https://www.youporn.com/information/#privacy). Failure to, when required, provide us and/or our third-party age verification service providers with information which will help us determine that you are over the age of majority required to have access to this Website and to view its Contents will lead to the termination or suspension of your access rights to all or part of this Website.

Back to Top

Changes to the Terms of Service

We may amend these Terms of Service, found at [https://www.youporn.com/information/#terms](https://www.youporn.com/information/#terms), from time to time. If you do, we will give you reasonable, advance notice, in a transparent manner, in text form, for example via a pop-up notification on the Website when logging on to your account, or via e-mail. Unless otherwise communicated by us, you will be deemed to have agreed to the changes unless you notify us, in writing and before the proposed effective date of the changes, that you do not agree. If you do not agree to the changes, you may no longer use our Website after the proposed changes come into effect. In this case, either you or we can terminate these Terms of Service with immediate effect.

Each updated version of this Terms of Service supersedes any prior versions as of the 'Last Modified' date found at the top, and any prior version(s) shall have no continuing legal effect.

Back to Top

About This Website

This Website allows for the general viewing of adult-oriented Content by Users, registered (whether directly though this Website or through certain other websites we own or operate) and unregistered. In addition, this Website allows for sharing and uploading of adult-oriented Content by Content Partners and Models.

This Website may contain links to third party sites that are not owned or controlled by this Website or its operator. This Website has no control over, and assumes no responsibility for, the Content, privacy policies, or practices of any third-party sites. In addition, this Website will not and cannot censor or edit the Content of any third-party site. By using any of this Website, you expressly relieve us from all liability arising from your use of any third-party sites. Accordingly, we encourage you to be aware when you leave this Website and to read the terms, conditions, and privacy policies of each other sites that you visit.

This Website is for your personal use and shall not be used for any commercial endeavor except those specifically endorsed or approved by this Website.

This Website is for adult-oriented Content. Other categories of Content may be rejected or deleted in our sole discretion.

You understand and acknowledge that when using this Website, you will be exposed to Content from a variety of sources, and that this Website is not responsible for the accuracy, usefulness, safety, or intellectual property rights of or relating to such Content. You further understand and acknowledge that you may be exposed to Content that is inaccurate, offensive, indecent, or objectionable to you, and you agree to waive, and hereby do waive, any legal or equitable rights or remedies you have or may have against this Website with respect thereto, and agree to indemnify and hold this Website, its operator, its parent corporation, its affiliates, licensors, service providers, officers, directors, employees, agents, successors and assigns, harmless to the fullest extent allowed by law regarding all matters related to your use of this Website.

Back to Top

Communication Preferences/Single Point of Contact

By using and registering as a User on this Website, you expressly and specifically consent to receiving electronic communications from us relating to your account. These communications may involve sending emails to your email address provided during registration, or posting communications on this Website (for example, through the members’ area on this Website upon login to ensure receipt in the event you have unsubscribed from email communications), or in the “My Account” or “My Profile” page and may include notices about your account (such as change in password or confirmation emails) and are part of your relationship with us. You agree that any notices, agreements, disclosures, or other communications that we send to you electronically will satisfy any legal communication requirements, including that such communications be in writing. You should maintain copies of electronic communications by printing a paper copy or saving an electronic copy.

In accordance with Articles 11 and 12 of Regulation (EU) 2022/2065 (the “**Digital Services Act**” or “**DSA**”), [dsa@youporn.com](mailto:dsa@youporn.com) is the designated, single point of contact for communications with recipients of the services offered herein, as well as for European Union Member State authorities, the Commission, and the Board for Digital Services. Please conduct all communications in English or Greek.

For any removal orders pursuant to Regulation (EU) 2021/784 (the **"Terrorist Content Online Regulation"** or **"TCO"**), [designated competent EU authorities](https://home-affairs.ec.europa.eu/policies/internal-security/counter-terrorism-and-radicalisation/prevention-radicalisation/terrorist-content-online/list-national-competent-authority-authorities-and-contact-points_en) can complete our [removal form](https://www.youporn.com/tco-removal). After submission of this form, you will receive further instructions by e-mail, which you may respond to with a removal order. For such removal orders, please use the template provided in [Annex I of the TCO](https://eur-lex.europa.eu/eli/reg/2021/784#:~:text=p.%20385).-,ANNEX%20I,-REMOVAL%20ORDER) and conduct all communication in either English or Greek.

Back to Top

Accessing this Website and Account Security

We reserve the right to withdraw or amend this Website, and any service or material we provide on this Website, in our sole discretion without notice. We will not be liable if for any reason all or any part of this Website is unavailable at any time or for any period. From time to time, we may restrict access to some parts of this Website, or the entire Website, to Users, including registered Users.

You are responsible for:

* making all arrangements necessary for you to have access to this Website, and
* ensuring that all persons who access this Website through your internet connection are aware of these Terms of Service and comply with them.

To access this Website or some of the resources it offers, you may be asked to provide certain registration details or other information. To know more about the information required to use this Website to upload Content, please refer to the Sections entitled "Rules Applicable to All Content and Uploaders on this Website", "Rules Applicable to Content Partners" and "Rules Applicable to Models", as well as the [Privacy Notice](https://www.youporn.com/information/#privacy). It is a condition of your use of this Website that all the information you provide on this Website is correct, current, and complete. You agree that all information you provide to register with this Website or otherwise, including but not limited to through the use of any interactive features on this Website, is governed by our [Privacy Notice](https://www.youporn.com/information/#privacy), and you consent to all actions we take with respect to your information consistent with our [Privacy Notice](https://www.youporn.com/information/#privacy).

If you choose, or are provided with, a username, password, or any other piece of information as part of our security procedures, you must treat such information as confidential, and you must not disclose it to any other person. You are fully responsible for all activities that occur under your username or password. You also acknowledge that your account is personal to you and agree not to provide any other person with access to this Website or portions of this Website using your username, password, or other security information. You agree to notify us immediately of any unauthorized access to or use of your username or password or any other breach of security by contacting us at: [support@youporn.com](mailto:support@youporn.com). You also agree to ensure that you exit from your account at the end of each session. You should use particular caution when accessing your account from a public or shared computer so that others are not able to view or record your password or other personal information. Although this Website will not be liable for your losses caused by any unauthorized use of your account, you may be liable for the losses of this Website or others due to such unauthorized use.

If you interact with us or with third-party service providers, you agree that all information that you provide are and will be accurate, complete, and current. You will review all policies and agreements applicable to use of third-party services. In the event you use our Website over mobile devices, you hereby acknowledge that your carrier’s normal rates and fees, such as excess broadband fees, will still apply.

We have the right to disable any username, password or other identifier, whether chosen by you or provided by us, at any time in our sole discretion for any or no reason, including if, in our opinion, you have violated any provision of these Terms of Service.

Back to Top

Limited, Conditional License to Use Our Intellectual Property

Youporn and associated logos and names are our trademarks and/or service marks. Other trademarks, service marks, names, and logos used on or through this Website, such as trademarks, service marks, names, or logos associated with third party content providers, are the trademarks, service marks, or logos of their respective owners. You are granted no right or license with respect to any of the aforesaid trademarks, service marks, or logos.

The inclusion of images or text containing the trademarks or service marks or the name or likeness of any person, including any celebrity, does not constitute an endorsement, express or implied, by any such person, of this Website or vice versa.

This Website and certain materials available on or through this Website are Content we own, authored, created, purchased, or licensed (collectively, our “**Works**”). Our Works may be protected by copyright, trademark, patent, trade secret, and/or other laws, and we reserve and retain all rights in our Works and this Website.

We grant you a conditional, revocable, non-sublicensable, non-transferable and non-exclusive and limited license to access and use our Website and Works solely for your personal use, conditioned upon your compliance with these Terms of Service and your agreement to display this Website whole and intact as presented by this Website’s host, complete with any advertising, to not interfere with the display of any advertising, and to not use ad blocking software of any kind. This limited license is further conditioned upon your agreement not to use any information obtained from or through this Website to block or interfere with the display of any advertising on this Website, or for the purpose of implementing, modifying, or updating any software or filter lists that block or interfere with the display of any advertising on this Website. Interference with the display of any advertising on this Website, use of ad blocking software to block or disable any advertising while viewing this Website, or use of information obtained from or through this Website to update any ad blocking software or filter lists, is prohibited, violates the conditions of your limited license to view this Website and Works and constitutes copyright infringement.

You may not otherwise reproduce, distribute, communicate to the public, make available, adapt, publicly perform, link to, or publicly display this Website and Works or any adaptations thereof unless expressly set forth herein. Such conduct would exceed the scope of your license and constitute copyright infringement.

This Website may provide an “embeddable player” feature, which you may incorporate into your own website for use in accessing the Content on this Website. You may not modify, build upon or block any portion or functionality of the embeddable player in any way, including but not limited to links back to this Website.

The above-described license is conditioned on your compliance with these Terms of Service, including, specifically, your agreement to view this Website whole and intact as presented by this Website’s host, complete with any advertising, and shall terminate upon termination of these Terms of Service. If you breach any provision of these Terms of Service, any license you have obtained will be automatically rescinded and terminated. In order to protect our rights, some Content made available on this Website may be controlled by digital rights management technologies, which will restrict how you may use the Content. You must not circumvent, remove, delete, disable, alter, or otherwise interfere with any digital rights management technology. Such conduct is prohibited by law.

You are not allowed to reproduce, download, distribute, transmit, broadcast, display, sell, license, alter, modify, or otherwise copy or reproduce our Works or Content that does not belong to you, in whole or in part.

Back to Top

Rules Applicable to All Content and Uploaders on this Website

To upload Content to this Website, you must be either a Content Partner or a Model, save and except if such Content is limited to comments, a cover picture and/or an avatar, in which case you must at least be a User with an unverified account on this Website. For the purposes of these Terms of Service, uploading Content onto this Website includes instances where such Content is first uploaded onto [www.pornhub.com](https://www.pornhub.com/) or another website that is owned or operated by us and shared therefrom onto this Website. If the information you provide for the creation of your account is not true and correct, you face the immediate termination of your account; where applicable, the immediate suspension of any and all pending payments from us to you; and we may, in our sole discretion, withhold payment of any owed amounts indefinitely, and you may be subject to legal sanctions.

You represent and warrant that with respect to all Content you will upload on this Website:

1. the Content does not contravene to any applicable laws and does not subject this Website to any claims, demands, lawsuits, regulatory actions or any actual, potential or risk of liability, or any threats thereof;
2. you own the rights to use the Content on this Website and that the Content does not infringe on the rights (including intellectual property rights) of a third party and, that you have obtained the consent and release for every individual appearing in your Content, including the right for you to use and upload the Content on this Website;
3. with respect to the Content, you, or the producer of the Content, have collected and maintained the records required under 18 U.S.C. § 2257 et. seq., as modified from time to time in compliance with the rules and regulations set forth in 28 C.F.R. § 75 et. seq., as modified from time to time, and any other applicable records keeping or age verification laws;
4. that Content Partner affirms that no individual appearing in the Content has been convicted of crimes relating to sexual assault, sexual exploitation of a minor, trafficking, and other related criminal offences;
5. the Content may be used for training purposes;
6. the Content is not a duplicate of another piece of Content uploaded by you or anyone else;
7. the Content complies with this Website’s [Terms of Service](https://www.youporn.com/information/#terms), and our [Privacy Notice](https://www.youporn.com/information/#privacy).

Failure to comply with these Terms of Service or any related contracts you will enter into with us, or should we determine that any of the statements above is untrue, or not complied with, we may, in our sole discretion, refuse to include the Content or any part thereof or any references to such Content on this Website, remove the Content in question from this Website, forfeit all accrued or pending earnings, cancel all current or pending payouts, terminate your account and take any measures necessary to minimize or eliminate any liability.

Back to Top

Online Safety Act - Rules Applicable to Australian Users

For the purposes of this section:

* **"Class 1A Material"** shall mean any material, by any medium, that depicts, or otherwise contains child sexual exploitation/child sexual abuse, extreme crime and/or violence, or material that is in support of terror and/or acts of terror.
* **"Class 1B Material"** shall mean any material that depicts or otherwise contains crime and/or violence (but not extreme drug or violence), or drug-related material.

Class 1A Material and Class 1B Material may hereinafter collectively be referred to as “Illicit Material”.

Per the provisions of the Online Safety Act (2021) (the **"OSA"**) Content Partners and Models hereby must ensure and subsequently warrants that:

* The Content uploaded or attempted to be uploaded to this Website is in adherence to our Terms described herein.
* Any audiovisual content uploaded or attempted to be uploaded to this Website does not contain Illicit Material.
* Content Partners and Models reserves the right to and shall take any action it deems necessary in order to limit, prevent, remove, or otherwise moderate any content which infringes the provisions of this section and/or any other, applicable terms. Content Partners and Models shall also ensure, to the extent possible, that you comply with the provisions of this section.
* We have a zero-tolerance policy towards the solicitation, access, generation, distribution, or storage of any content that involves the depiction of children or features Class 1A Material in any capacity. All child sexual exploitation/abuse material that we identify or are made aware of will result in the immediate removal of the content in question as well as the immediate removal of its uploader from this Website. Without prejudice to all other rights reserved for action against the above (including account suspension, removal of infringing content etc.), we report all cases of apparent child sexual exploitation/abuse material to the National Center for Missing and Exploited Children.

Back to Top

Obligation to comply with Records Keeping Requirements under 18 U.S.C. §2257

You certify that the Content you upload to this Website has been produced and records are being kept in accordance with 18 U.S.C. § 2257 et. seq., as modified from time to time, with the rules and regulations set forth in 28 C.F.R. § 75 et. seq., as modified from time to time, and any other applicable records keeping or age verification laws. Upon our request, you shall promptly deliver us legible copies (as may be lawfully redacted), of valid (as of the date of production of the Content) recognizable governmental photo identifications for any or all individuals appearing in any or all of your Content (demonstrating that each were at least 18 years of age on the day the Content was produced) together with the required identification forms, documents and releases. In this context, when we refer to all individuals appearing in the Content, we mean, without limitation, filmed, photographed, or recorded individuals or individuals in any way in the Content, whether appearing nude, semi-nude or fully clothed, engaging in simulated or actual sexual intercourse (including solo scenes). We do not accept or accommodate voice over or sounds from persons less than 18 years of age appearing in the background or synced with the Content whether featured or not. Your failure to promptly deliver the requested information upon request, may lead to the temporary or permanent suspension of your account. You will, at your own expense, indemnify, defend and hold us harmless from, any and all liabilities, losses, damages, fines, fees, penalties, costs and expenses (including reasonable attorneys’ fees) incurred or suffered by us from any claim arising or resulting from your failure or negligence to comply with maintenance of any legally mandated records.

You acknowledge that you are solely responsible for the activity that occurs on your account. Please note that you may not permit any other person to use your account and that you must immediately inform us of any apparent breach of security, such as loss, theft or unauthorized disclosure or use of a screen name or password. You may never use anyone else’s account, just as no one can ever use yours.

You will be liable for any losses incurred by us due to the unauthorized use of your account. We are not liable for your losses caused by any unauthorized use of your account, and you specifically waive any such claim and agree to defend and indemnify us against any such claims made against your account by third parties.

To the extent you voluntarily create a User profile to participate in certain select services offered by us, your profile (and its Contents) may be searchable by other Users registered through this Website and others partnered or networked with us. Likewise, your profile (and its Contents) may be searchable by publicly available search engines.

You understand that we do not guarantee any confidentiality with respect to any Content you contribute. Subject to what is permitted under applicable law, you are free to choose the type of Content you produce and post or publish. You shall be solely responsible for your own Content and the consequences of posting or publishing such Content.

We are not responsible for any Content that violates community standards in your community. If you are seeking information regarding any illegal or inappropriate activities, you agree to leave this Website immediately. We expect and demand that you comply with all applicable laws when using this Website and when submitting or posting Content to this Website. If you are unsure whether or not Content will violate a law, you are urged to contact an attorney prior to posting the Content. We cannot enforce every jurisdiction’s laws for all Content that is posted to this Website. As such, we are not responsible for the Content of this Website.

You must evaluate, and bear all risks associated with, the use of any Content, including any reliance on the accuracy, completeness, or usefulness, or lawfulness of such Content. In this regard, you acknowledge that you may not rely on any Content created by us or Content transmitted to this Website. You are responsible for all your Content that is uploaded, posted, emailed, transmitted, or otherwise made available via this Website.

If we have a reason to suspect that your Content violates any third party right, including without limitation any copyright, trademark, or property right, we can require you to provide us with written evidence of your ownership of, or right to use, the material in question. If we require such written evidence, you agree to provide it to us within five (5) working days of the date of our request. Your failure to provide us with such required written evidence within that timeframe may lead to the immediate termination of your account, us demanding compensation from you for any accrued costs and damages related to such Content.

You shall be solely responsible for your own Content and the consequences of posting, uploading, publishing, transmitting, or otherwise making available your Content on this Website. You understand and acknowledge that you are responsible for any Content you submit or contribute, and you, not us, have full responsibility for such Content, including its legality, reliability, accuracy, and appropriateness. We do not control Content you submit or contribute, and we do not make any guarantee whatsoever related to Content submitted or contributed by Users. Under no circumstances will we be liable or responsible in any way for any claim related to Content submitted or contributed by Users.

You affirm, represent, and warrant that you own or have the necessary licenses, rights, consents, and permissions to publish Content you submit; and you license to this Website all patent, trademark, trade secret, copyright, or other proprietary rights in and to such Content for publication on this Website pursuant to these Terms of Service.

You further agree that Content you submit to this Website will not contain third party copyrighted material, or material that is subject to other third-party proprietary rights, unless you have permission from the rightful owner of the material, or you are otherwise legally entitled to post the material and to grant to this Website all of the license rights granted herein.

You agree and understand that this Website (and its successors’ and affiliates’) may make use of your Content for promotional or commercial purposes and to render the services pursuant to these Terms of Services. For clarity, you retain all of your ownership rights in your Content. Without regard to the Last Modified date, by submitting Content to this Website, you hereby grant this Website’s operators an unlimited, worldwide, perpetual, non-exclusive, royalty-free, sublicensable, and transferable license to use, reproduce, publish, distribute, broadcast, market, create derivative works of, adapt, translate, publicly display, communicate, or perform, make available or otherwise use all of the Content, including without limitation for promoting and redistributing part or all of this Website (and derivative works thereof) in any media formats and through any media channels. You also waive to the full extent permitted by law any and all claims against us related to moral rights in the Content. In no circumstances will we be liable to you for any exploitation of any Content that you post. You also hereby grant each User of this Website a non-exclusive, royalty free license to access your Content through this Website as permitted under these Terms of Service. You hereby understand and agree that you may not use this Website to allow other Users to download or otherwise save the Content you post (or any part thereof). The above licenses granted by you in video Content you submit to this Website terminate within a commercially reasonable time after you remove or delete your Content from this Website. You understand and agree, however, that this Website may retain, but not display, distribute, or perform, server copies of your videos that have been removed or deleted. The above licenses granted by you in User comments you submit are perpetual and irrevocable. This Website do not endorse any Content submitted by any User or other licensor, or any opinion, recommendation, or advice expressed therein, and this Website expressly disclaim any and all liability in connection with Content. This Website does not permit copyright infringing activities and infringement of intellectual property rights on this Website, and this Website will remove all Content if properly notified that such Content infringes on another’s intellectual property rights. This Website reserves the right to remove Content without prior notice. This Website reserves the right to hash any uploaded Content for training purposes including but not limited to, training for identifying, or combating illegal activities and these hashes may be shared with third parties, including law enforcement agencies.

All Content you submit must comply with the Content standards set out in these Terms of Service.

If any of the Content that you post or through this Website contain ideas, suggestions, documents, and/or proposals to us, we will have no obligation of confidentiality, express or implied, with respect to such Content, and we shall be entitled to use, exploit, or disclose (or choose not to use or disclose) such Content in our sole discretion without any obligation to you whatsoever (i.e. you will not be entitled to any compensation of any kind from us under any circumstances).

Back to Top

Rules Applicable to Content Partners

If you want to become a Content Partner and post Content on this Website, you must first join the Pornhub Content Partner Program and agree to its terms and conditions.

Back to Top

Rules Applicable to Models

If you want to become a Model and post Content through this Website, you must first join the Pornhub Model Partner Program and agree to its terms and conditions.

We may, in our sole discretion, decline your application to join our community of Content providers for any reason.

You may be asked to provide a valid email address for verification purposes. You will choose your own screen name, which must be unique to you, not offensive to others, and not in violation of another’s copyright or trademark. You will also choose your password, which you can change later. It is imperative that you do not let anyone else use your account (you must keep your password secret and secure). Certain changes to your personal information such as your name and screen name can only be made by our staff. Therefore, if your information appears incorrect or needs to be changed you may need to contact our staff to have this done.

Before you are able upload Content on this Website, you need to verify your identity. In order to do so, you need to submit to us high-res images or scans of a minimum of one to two information documents, containing your date of birth, expiration date of the ID, your photo, your full legal name and your address. This could be, for example, your driver’s license (in countries where a national ID is not mandatory), international passport, citizenship card, state ID, national passport, or your national ID card. The other form of identification may be a utility bill. If all the required information is set out on your government-issued photo ID, you do not need a second document. We may, in our sole discretion, require you to provide us multiple forms of identification to establish proof of adulthood and identity. Facial verification and an assessment of the authenticity of the aforementioned documents is also required in the context of our verification of your age and identity. Our collection, use and disclosure of such information and documentation is governed by our [Privacy Notice](https://www.youporn.com/information/#privacy).

Back to Top

Models’ Commission

Models will be entitled to receive the model program advertising share revenue (a percentage of the ad revenue that the video earns) on free to watch videos on this Websites.

You will not receive monthly a statement showing any amounts you earned. However, you will be able to view amounts earned in your account. Payments are generally made within ten (10) business days after the end of each month (although, depending on the payment method used, it may take longer for you to actually receive your payment); provided, however, that payment will be made only when the minimum payout, based on net income, of one hundred dollars (US$100.00) has been reached. Any amount below one hundred dollars (US$100.00) will be carried over until the minimum payout has been reached and will be paid on the next following payment date. If you provide us with incorrect payment details, any fees for chargebacks resulting from such incorrect payment details will be offset against any amounts otherwise payable to you.

In the event you violate any part of the present Terms of Service, or if you violate any third party right, including without limitation any copyright, property, or privacy right, or where a third-party claims that all or any part of your Content caused it damage, we may, in our sole discretion, withhold indefinitely payments to you.

We remind you that it is your sole duty and obligation to fulfill all tax obligations with regard to your activities for us, including but not limited to registration, declaration, and payment obligations related to income taxes and VAT. If we assist you with these obligations, it does not release you from your obligations. It is your duty to inform us in a timely manner of changes to your personal data such as an address change or a new email.

Back to Top

Use of Website

You agree that you will only use this Website and our services for the lawful purposes expressly permitted and contemplated by these Terms of Service. You may not use this Website and our services for any other purposes, including but not limited to commercial purposes, without our express written consent.

You agree that you will view this Website and its Content unaltered and unmodified. You acknowledge and understand that you are prohibited from modifying this Website or eliminating any of the Content of this Website, including ads. You must not circumvent, remove, delete, disable, alter, or otherwise interfere with any age and biometric verification processes, technologies or security tools used anywhere on this Website or in connection with our services. By using this Website, you expressly agree to accept advertising served on and through this Website and to refrain from using ad blocking software or to disable ad blocking software before visiting this Website.

Content is provided to you AS IS. You may access Content for your information and personal use solely as intended through the provided functionality of this Website and as permitted under these Terms of Service. You shall not download, copy, reproduce, distribute, transmit, broadcast, display, sell, license, or otherwise exploit any Content which are not permitted in the Terms of Service.

Back to Top

Prohibited Uses and Reporting

If you see any Content you suspect violates applicable law, third party rights, or these Terms of Service, please report such Content to us, using the electronic form available at [https://www.youporn.com/information//content-removal/](https://www.youporn.com/content-removal), or the “**Flag This Video**” button available below each piece of content. Further, the Website does not permit any form of revenge porn, blackmail, or intimidation, and such violations may also be reported using the content removal link herein.

We will give due priority to reports submitted by our Trusted Flaggers, who have been granted this status by the Digital Services Coordinator of the relevant Member State of the European Union. In addition, Non-Governmental Organizations and Statutory Offices can also join the Pornhub Trusted Flagger Program.

You agree that you will not use or attempt to use any method, device, software, or routine to harm others or interfere with the functioning of this Website or use and/or monitor any information in or related to this Website for any unauthorized purpose.

In addition to the general restrictions above, the following restrictions and conditions apply specifically to your use of Content. Any determination regarding breach of any of the following is final. Please review the following list of prohibited uses carefully before using this Website. Specifically, you agree not to use any of this Website to:

* violate any law or encourage or provide instructions to another to do so;
* act in a manner that negatively affects other Users’ ability to use this Website, including without limitation by engaging in conduct that is harmful, threatening, abusive, inflammatory, intimidating, violent or encouraging of violence to people or animals, harassing, stalking, invasive of another’s privacy, or racially, ethnically, or otherwise objectionable;
* provide or allow access or viewing to or by, or engage and/or interact with, any person who has not yet reached at least eighteen (18) years of age, or older in any other location in which eighteen (18) is not the minimum age of majority in the applicable jurisdiction;
* post any Content that depicts any person under 18 years of age (or older in any other location in which 18 is not the minimum age of majority) whether real, simulated or animated;
* post any Content for which you have not maintained written documentation sufficient to confirm that all subjects of your posts are, in fact, over eighteen (18) years of age, or older in any other location in which eighteen (18) is not the minimum age of majority in the applicable jurisdiction at the time the Content was created post any Content depicting whether actual, realistically portrayed and/or simulated, or animated underage sexual activity, non-consensual sexual activity, revenge porn, blackmail, intimidation, snuff, torture, death, violence, incest, racial slurs, or hate speech, (either orally or via the written word);
* post any Content that contains falsehoods or misrepresentations that could damage this Website or any third party;
* post any Content that is obscene, illegal, unlawful, fraudulent, defamatory, libelous, harassing, hateful, racially or ethnically offensive, or encourages conduct that would be considered a criminal offense, give rise to civil liability, violate any law, or is otherwise inappropriate;
* post any Content containing unsolicited or unauthorized advertising, promotional materials, spam, junk mail, chain letters, pyramid schemes, or any other form of unauthorized solicitation;
* post any Content containing sweepstakes, contests, or lotteries, or otherwise related to gambling;
* post any Content containing copyrighted materials, or materials protected by other intellectual property laws, that you do not own or for which you have not obtained all necessary written permissions and releases;
* post any Content which impersonates another person or falsely states or otherwise misrepresents your affiliation with a person;
* use this Website (or post any Content that) in any way that promotes or facilitates prostitution, solicitation of prostitution, human trafficking, or sex trafficking;
* use this Website to arrange any in-person meetings for purposes of sexual activity for hire or consideration;
* deploy programs, software, or applications designed to interrupt, destroy or limit the functionality of any computer software or hardware or telecommunications equipment, including by engaging in any denial-of-service attack or similar conduct;
* deploy or use programs, software or applications designed to harm, interfere with the operation of, or access in an unauthorized manner, services, networks, servers, or other infrastructure;
* exceed your authorized access to any portion of this Website;
* remove, delete, alter, circumvent, avoid, or bypass any digital rights management technology, encryption or security tools used anywhere on this Website or in connection with our services;
* remove, delete, alter, circumvent, avoid, or bypass any age verification processes, technologies or security tools used anywhere on this Website or in connection with our services;
* collect or store personal data about anyone or use, post or make unauthorized use of anyone else's information, image, likeness, or Content;
* alter or modify without permission any part of this Website or its Content, including ads;
* obtain or attempt to access or otherwise obtain any Content or information through any means not intentionally made available or provided for through this Website;
* exploit errors in design, features which are not documented, and/or bugs to gain access that would otherwise not be available.

Additionally, you agree not to:

* use this Website in any manner that could disable, overburden, damage, or impair the site or interfere with any other party’s use of this Website, including their ability to engage in real time activities through this Website;
* use any robot, spider, or other automatic device, process, or means to access this Website for any purpose, including monitoring or copying any of the material on this Website without our prior written consent;
* use any manual process to download, monitor or copy any of the material on this Website or for any other unauthorized purpose;
* use any information obtained from or through this Website to block or interfere with the display of any advertising on this Website, or for the purpose of implementing, modifying or updating any software or filter lists that block or interfere with the display of any advertising on this Website;
* use any device, bots, scripts, software, or routine that interferes with the proper working of this Website or that shortcut or alter Website functions to run or appear in ways that are not intended by this Website’s design;
* introduce or upload any viruses, trojan horses, worms, logic bombs, time bombs, cancelbots, corrupted files or any other similar software, program, or material which is malicious or technologically harmful or that that may damage the operation of another’s property or of this Website’s or our services;
* attempt to gain unauthorized access to, interfere with, damage, or disrupt any parts of this Website, the server on which this Website are stored, or any server, computer, or database connected to this Website;
* remove any copyright or other proprietary notices from our Website or any of the materials contained therein;
* remove any copyright or other proprietary notices from our Website or any of the materials contained therein;
* otherwise attempt to interfere with the proper working of this Website.

Back to Top

Monitoring and Enforcement; Termination

We have the right but not the obligation to take any of the following actions, including pursuant to when we detect, or are notified of, any activity or Content uploaded to the Website that infringes applicable laws, rights of third parties, or these Terms of Service. When deciding on appropriate action, we consider all relevant factors such as the frequency, severity, and impact of a violation, as well as any measures previously imposed on an infringer:

* Issue a written warning to the infringer. Before we temporarily or permanently suspend an infringer’s access to our services following provision of manifestly illegal Content or action by such infringer we may issue a warning to the infringer, provided such warning would not conflict with the purposes of the moderation decision. Examples of misuse that may be sanctioned with a suspension or termination include, but are not limited to, the frequent uploading of Content that violates applicable law, third party rights, or these Terms of Service, or the uploading of Content that manifestly and severely violates applicable law, third party rights, or these Terms of Service, such as Child Sexual Abuse Material or revenge porn.
* Restrict the visibility or other accessibility of Content.
* Restrict the access of, suspend, or terminate a User’s account.
* Restricting, suspending, or otherwise terminating a Content Partner or Model’s ability to monetize their Content.
* Restricting, suspending, or withholding earnings and payouts.
* Report the infringer to law enforcement authorities.

We may also:

* remove or refuse to post any Content you submit or contribute to this Website for any or no reason in our sole discretion, including, without limitation, if any information or documentation provided by you is inadequate, incomplete, or inaccurate or does not allow us to assess and confirm your identity.
* monitor any communication occurring on or through this Website to confirm compliance with these Terms of Service, the security of this Website, or any legal obligation;
* take appropriate legal action, including without limitation, referral to law enforcement, for any illegal or unauthorized use of this Website.

If we have reason to believe that Content violates any applicable law, third party right, or these Terms of Service, we may take appropriate interim actions (as described herein), to prevent potential harm to our further investigation. In deciding on the appropriate and proportionate course of action, we will give due consideration to the legitimate interests of the impacted User, any other potentially affected rights holders, and our own legitimate interests. In particular, we will assess the nature of the Content concerned, the gravity of the respective violation or illegality, and any indications on whether or not the Content contributor was at fault. In case an investigation was prompted following report by a User, we will also consider the explanatory information and evidence provided by such User and, if available, the reporting User’s submission history.

We use a variety of procedures and tools to identify, review and moderate Content. This includes both human and automated review, or a combination of both, depending on what is appropriate and required in each individual case.

Automated review may include the use of systems which assist us in identifying infringing Content, determining the prioritization of certain issues, and applying appropriate measures. Content may be compared against databases of digitally finger-printed content and other, similar repositories, such as (but not limited to) YouTube’s CSAI Match. Automated review may be subject to further, manual verification, in the context of which Content and measures may be reassessed.

Without limiting the foregoing, we have the right to fully cooperate with any law enforcement authorities or court order requesting or directing us to disclose the identity or other information of anyone posting any Content on or through this Website. YOU WAIVE AND HOLD US, OUR OFFICERS, DIRECTORS, EMPLOYEES, SUCCESSORS, AND ASSIGNS HARMLESS FROM ANY CLAIMS RESULTING FROM ANY ACTION TAKEN BY US AS A CONSEQUENCE OF DISCLOSING PERSONAL INFORMATION IN RELATION TO DATA DISCLOSURE REQUESTS FROM LAW ENFORCEMENT AUTHORITIES.

This Website takes a powerful stand against any form of child exploitation or human trafficking. If we discover that any Content involves underage individuals, or any form of force, fraud, or coercion, we will remove the Content and submit a report to the proper law enforcement authorities. If you become aware of any such Content, you agree to report it to this Website by contacting [legal@youporn.com](mailto:legal@youporn.com).

To maintain our services in a manner we deem appropriate for our venue and to the maximum extent permitted by applicable laws, this Website may, but will not have any obligation to display, reject, refuse to post, store, maintain, accept, or remove any Content posted (including, without limitation, private messages, public comments, public group chat messages, private group chat messages, or private instant messages) by you, and we may, in our sole discretion, delete, move, re-format, remove, or refuse to post or otherwise make use of Content without notice or any liability to you or any third party in connection with our operation of this Website in an appropriate manner. In addition, this Website may, but will not have any obligation to, review and monitor private messages, public comments, public group chat messages, private group chat messages, or private instant messages posted by you. Without limitation, we may do so to address Content that comes to our attention that we believe is offensive, obscene, violent, harassing, threatening, abusive, illegal, or otherwise objectionable or inappropriate, or to enforce the rights of third parties or these Terms of Service or any applicable additional terms, including, without limitation, the Content restrictions set forth herein.

We assume no liability for any action or inaction regarding transmissions, communications, or Content provided by any User or third party. We have no liability or responsibility to anyone for performance or non-performance of the activities described in this section.

Back to Top

Complaint Handling Procedure

If we take any action concerning you, your account, or any Content that you attempted to or uploaded on the Website, as set out in the section “Monitoring and Enforcement; Termination”, you may lodge a complaint against such decision. Similarly, you may lodge a complaint if you disagree with our decision following a notice you submitted for Content reporting or removal.

In either case, the deadline for submission of a complaint is six (6) months after notification of the respective decision has been communicated to you. To lodge a complaint you may email [dsa@youporn.com](mailto:dsa@youporn.com) from the email associated with your account or wherefrom notice of the decision has been communicated, and the correspondence must include as much information as possible to allow us to investigate your complaint, and an explanation of the reason(s) for which you believe your complaint to be justified.

We handle complaints in a timely, non-discriminatory, diligent, and objective manner. We may reverse previous decisions if a complaint sufficiently demonstrates that:

* The Content to which our decision related did not in fact violate applicable law, third party rights, or these Terms of Service.
* Our prior decision to not act on a notice was unjustified.
* Our prior decision was unjustified or disproportionate in any other manner.

Back to Top

Abuse of Reporting and/or Complaint Handling System

We may suspend your access to our reporting and internal complaint-handling systems for a reasonable period of time if you frequently submit notices or complaints that are manifestly unfounded. Prior to such suspension we may issue a warning, provided that this does not conflict with the purpose of the suspension or with other, appropriate measures that may be applied. When deciding on the suspension, we consider factors such as the frequency, severity, and impact of your violation(s), as well as any prior measures imposed. Examples of misuse of our reporting and/or complaint-handling system that may be subject to suspension include, but are not limited to:

* Frequently submitting multiple, identical, and unfounded notices or complaints.
* Frequently submitting notices or complaints that are obviously unfounded.

Back to Top

Account Termination Policy

While pornographic and adult-oriented Content is accepted, this Website reserves the right to decide whether Content is appropriate or violates these Terms of Service for reasons other than copyright infringement and violations of intellectual property rights, such as, but not limited to, obscene or defamatory material. In line with the provisions of the section titled “Monitoring and Enforcement; Termination”, we may, in our sole discretion, issue warning or take analogous, appropriate action (on repeat offences) against such infringements.

If you violate the letter or spirit of these Terms of Service, or otherwise create risk or possible legal exposure for us, we can terminate access to this Website or stop providing all or part of this Website to you for any reasons at our convenience.

Back to Top

Copyright and Other Intellectual Property

This Website operates a clear [Copyright Policy](https://www.youporn.com/information/#dmca) in relation to any Content alleged to infringe the copyright of a third party. If you believe that any Content violates your copyright, please see our [Copyright Policy](https://www.youporn.com/information/#dmca) for instructions on sending us a notice of copyright infringement. As part of our [Copyright Policy](https://www.youporn.com/information/#dmca), this Website will terminate User access to this Website if, under appropriate circumstances, a User has been determined to be a repeat infringer and in line with the provisions of the section titled “Monitoring and Enforcement; Termination” of these Terms.

This Website is not in a position to mediate trademark disputes between Users and trademark owners. Accordingly, we encourage trademark owners to resolve any dispute directly with the User in question or seek any resolution in court or by other judicial means. If you’re sure you want to report Content on this Website that you believe infringes your trademark, you can do so by contacting us at legal@youporn.com. This Website is willing to perform a limited investigation of reasonable complaints and will remove Content in clear cases of infringement. Only the trademark owner or their authorized representative may file a report of trademark infringement. Please note that we regularly provide the rights owner’s name, your email address, and the details of your report to the person who posted the Content you are reporting. This person may contact you with the information you provide.

Back to Top

Reliance on Information Posted

The information presented on or through this Website is made available solely for general information purposes. We do not warrant the accuracy, completeness, or usefulness of this information. Any reliance you place on such information is strictly at your own risk. We disclaim all liability and responsibility arising from any reliance placed on such materials by you or any other visitor to this Website, or by anyone who may be informed of any of its Contents.

This Website includes Content provided by third parties, including materials provided by other Users, bloggers and third-party licensors, syndicators, aggregators, and/or reporting services. All statements and/or opinions expressed in these materials, and all articles and responses to questions and other Content, other than the Content provided by us, are solely the opinions and the responsibility of the person or entity providing those materials. These materials do not necessarily reflect our opinion. We are not responsible, or liable to you or any third party, for the Content or accuracy of any materials provided by any third parties.

Back to Top

Changes to this Website

We may update the Content on this Website from time to time, but its Content is not necessarily complete or up to date. Any of the material on this Website may be out of date at any given time, and we are under no obligation to update such material.

Back to Top

Information about You and Your Visits to this Website

All information we collect on this Website is subject to our [Privacy Notice](https://www.youporn.com/information/#privacy). By using this Website, you acknowledge that you have read and understand the terms of the [Privacy Notice](https://www.youporn.com/information/#privacy) and that you consent to all actions taken by us with respect to your information in compliance with the [Privacy Notice](https://www.youporn.com/information/#privacy).

Back to Top

Collection and Use of Your Usage Information by Advertisers and Others

This Website allows others to display advertisements using this Website. These third parties use technology to deliver advertisements you see using this Website directly to your browser. In doing so, they may automatically receive your internet protocol (IP) address. Others that place advertising using this Website may have the ability to use cookies and/or web beacons to collect information, including information about your usage of this Website. We do not control the processes that advertisers use to collect information. However, IP addresses, cookies and web beacons alone generally cannot be used to identify individuals, only machines. Therefore, advertisers and others whose advertisements or Content may be provided through the service generally will not know who you are unless you provide additional information to them, by responding to an advertisement, by entering into an agreement with them, or by some other means.

Back to Top

Linking to this Website and Social Media Features

You may link to this Website, provided you do so in a way that is fair and legal and does not damage our reputation or take advantage of it, but you must not establish a link in such a way as to suggest any form of association, approval, or endorsement on our part without our express written consent.

This Website may provide certain social media features that enable you to:

* link from your own or certain third-party websites to certain Content on this Website;
* send emails or other communications with certain Content, or links to certain Content, on this Website;
* cause limited portions of Content on this Website to be displayed or appear to be displayed on your own or certain third-party websites.
* You may use these features solely as they are provided by us and solely with respect to the Content they are displayed with and otherwise in accordance with any additional terms and conditions we provide with respect to such features. Subject to the foregoing, you must not:
* cause this Website or portions of this Website to be displayed, or appear to be displayed by, for example, framing, deep linking or in-line linking, on any other site,
* otherwise take any action with respect to the materials on this Website that is inconsistent with any other provision of these Terms of Service.

The sites from which you are linking, or on which you make certain Content accessible, must comply in all respects with the Content standards set out in these Terms of Service.

You agree to cooperate with us in causing any unauthorized framing or linking immediately to cease. We reserve the right to withdraw linking permission without notice.

We may disable all or any social media features and any links at any time without notice in our sole discretion.

Back to Top

Links from this Website

If this Website contains links to other sites and resources provided by third parties, these links are provided for your convenience only. This includes links contained in advertisements, including banner advertisements and sponsored links. We have no control over, and assume no responsibility for, the Contents, privacy policies, or practices of those sites or resources, and accept no responsibility for them or for any loss or damage that may arise from your use of them. Inclusion of, linking to, or permitting the use or installation of any third-party site, applications, software, Content, or advertising does not imply approval or endorsement thereof by us. If you decide to access any of the third-party sites linked to this Website, you do so entirely at your own risk and subject to the terms and conditions of use for such sites. Further, you agree to release us from any and all liability arising from your use of any third-party website, Content, service, or software accessed through this Website.

Your communications or dealings with, or participation in promotions of, sponsors, advertisers, or other third parties found through this Website, are solely between you and such third parties. You agree that this Website shall not be responsible or liable for any loss or damage of any sort incurred as the result of any dealings with such sponsors, third parties or advertisers, or as the result of their presence on this Website.

Back to Top

Permitted Disclosures of Personal Information

This Website generally does not collect personally identifiable information (data such as your name, email address, password, and the Content of your communications) unless you submit or communicate Content through this Website or register with us to use certain features of this Website. This Website will not disclose any personally identifiable information they collects or obtains except: (i) as described in these Terms of Service or our [Privacy Notice](https://www.youporn.com/information/#privacy); (ii) after obtaining your permission to a specific use or disclosure; (iii) if this Website is required to do so in order to comply with any valid legal process or governmental request (such as a court order, search warrant, subpoena, civil discovery request, or statutory requirement) and may in our sole discretion advise you of such process or request; (iv) as required to protect this Website’s property, safety, or operations, or the property or safety of others; or (v) to a person that acquires this Website, or the assets of this Website’s operator in connection with which such information has been collected or used; or (vi) as otherwise required by law. If this Website is required to respond to or comply with any of these information requests, we reserve the right to charge you with the cost of responding to or complying with such information request, including, but not limited to, costs of research, copies, media storage, mail, and document delivery, as well as any applicable legal fees.

This Website will have access to all information that you have submitted or created for as long as reasonably required to comply with or investigate any information requests, or to protect this Website. To enforce these Terms of Services, to protect intellectual property rights, to comply with legal processes and the law, and to protect this Website, you agree to allow this Website to access your information.

Back to Top

Indemnification

To the extent permitted by applicable law, you agree to defend, indemnify and hold harmless this Website, its site operator, its parent corporation, its affiliates, licensors, service providers, officers, directors, employees, agents, successors and assigns from and against any and all claims, damages, judgments, awards, obligations, losses, liabilities, costs or debt, and expenses (including but not limited to attorney’s fees) arising from: (i) your use of and access to this Website; (ii) your violation of any term of these Terms of Service; (iii) your violation of any third party right, including without limitation any copyright, property, or privacy right; or (iv) any claim that your Content caused damage to a third party. This defense and indemnification obligation will survive these Terms of Service and your use of this Website. You agree that we shall have the sole right and obligation to control the legal defense against any such claims, demands, or litigation, including the right to select counsel of our choice and to compromise or settle any such claims, demands, or litigation.

Back to Top

Disclaimers

YOU USE THE WEBSITE AT YOUR SOLE RISK. WE PROVIDE THE WEBSITE "AS IS" AND "AS AVAILABLE". TO THE FULLEST EXTENT PERMITTED BY LAW, THE WEBSITE, DISCLAIM ALL WARRANTIES OF ANY KIND RELATED TO THE WEBSITE AND GOODS OR SERVICES OBTAINED THROUGH THE WEBSITE, WHETHER EXPRESS OR IMPLIED, INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, THE IMPLIED WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY, FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE, AND NON-INFRINGEMENT. YOU WILL BE SOLELY RESPONSIBLE FOR ANY DAMAGE TO YOUR COMPUTER SYSTEM OR LOSS OF DATA THAT RESULTS FROM YOUR USE OF THE WEBSITE. WE MAKE NO WARRANTY OR REPRESENTATION ABOUT THE ACCURACY OR COMPLETENESS OF THE WEBSITE’S CONTENT OR THE CONTENT OF ANY SITES LINKED TO THE WEBSITE OR THAT THE WEBSITE WILL MEET YOUR REQUIREMENTS AND ASSUME NO LIABILITY OR RESPONSIBILITY FOR ANY (I) ERRORS, MISTAKES, OR INACCURACIES OF CONTENT, (II) PERSONAL INJURY OR PROPERTY DAMAGE, OF ANY NATURE WHATSOEVER, RESULTING FROM YOUR ACCESS TO AND USE OF THE WEBSITE OR OUR SERVICES, (III) ANY UNAUTHORIZED ACCESS TO OR USE OF OUR SECURE SERVERS AND/OR ANY AND ALL PERSONAL INFORMATION AND/OR FINANCIAL INFORMATION STORED THEREIN, (IV) ANY INTERRUPTION OR CESSATION OF TRANSMISSION TO OR FROM THE WEBSITE OR OUR SERVICES, (IV) ANY BUGS, VIRUSES, TROJAN HORSES, OR THE LIKE WHICH MAY BE TRANSMITTED TO OR THROUGH THE WEBSITE OR OUR SERVICES BY ANY THIRD PARTY, AND/OR (V) ANY ERRORS OR OMISSIONS IN ANY CONTENT OR FOR ANY LOSS OR DAMAGE OF ANY KIND INCURRED AS A RESULT OF THE USE OF ANY CONTENT POSTED, TRANSMITTED, OR OTHERWISE MADE AVAILABLE VIA THE WEBSITE OR OUR SERVICES. THE WEBSITE DOES NOT WARRANT, ENDORSE, GUARANTEE, OR ASSUME RESPONSIBILITY FOR ANY PRODUCT OR SERVICE ADVERTISED OR OFFERED BY A THIRD PARTY THROUGH THE WEBSITE OR OUR SERVICES OR ANY HYPERLINKED SERVICES OR FEATURED IN ANY BANNER OR OTHER ADVERTISING AND, THE WEBSITE WILL NOT BE A PARTY TO OR IN ANY WAY BE RESPONSIBLE FOR MONITORING ANY TRANSACTION BETWEEN YOU AND THIRD-PARTY PROVIDERS OF PRODUCTS OR SERVICES. AS WITH THE PURCHASE OF A PRODUCT OR SERVICE THROUGH ANY MEDIUM OR IN ANY ENVIRONMENT, YOU SHOULD USE YOUR BEST JUDGMENT AND EXERCISE CAUTION WHERE APPROPRIATE.

NO INFORMATION OBTAINED BY YOU FROM US OR THROUGH THE WEBSITE SHALL CREATE ANY WARRANTY NOT EXPRESSLY STATED IN THESE TERMS.

Back to Top

Limitation of Liability

IN NO EVENT SHALL THE WEBSITE, ITS OFFICERS, DIRECTORS, OR EMPLOYEES BE LIABLE TO YOU FOR ANY DIRECT, INDIRECT, INCIDENTAL, SPECIAL, PUNITIVE, OR CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES WHATSOEVER RESULTING FROM ANY (I) ERRORS, MISTAKES, OR INACCURACIES OF CONTENT, (II) PERSONAL INJURY OR PROPERTY DAMAGE, OF ANY NATURE WHATSOEVER, RESULTING FROM YOUR ACCESS TO AND USE OF OUR WEBSITE OR SERVICES, (III) ANY UNAUTHORIZED ACCESS TO OR USE OF OUR SECURE SERVERS AND/OR ANY AND ALL PERSONAL INFORMATION AND/OR FINANCIAL INFORMATION STORED THEREIN, (IV) ANY INTERRUPTION OR CESSATION OF TRANSMISSION TO OR FROM OUR WEBSITE, (IV) ANY BUGS, VIRUSES, TROJAN HORSES, OR THE LIKE, WHICH MAY BE TRANSMITTED TO OR THROUGH OUR WEBSITE OR SERVICES BY ANY THIRD PARTY, (V) ANY ERRORS OR OMISSIONS IN ANY CONTENT OR FOR ANY LOSS OR DAMAGE OF ANY KIND INCURRED AS A RESULT OF YOUR USE OF ANY CONTENT TRANSMITTED, OR OTHERWISE MADE AVAILABLE VIA OUR WEBSITE OR SERVICES, AND/OR (VI) INTERACTIONS YOU HAVE WITH THIRD-PARTY ADVERTISEMENTS OR SERVICE PROVIDERS, OR THIRD-PARTY SITES, FOUND ON OR THROUGH THIS WEBSITE, INCLUDING PAYMENT AND DELIVERY OF RELATED GOODS OR SERVICES, AND ANY OTHER TERMS, CONDITIONS, POLICIES, WARRANTIES OR REPRESENTATIONS ASSOCIATED WITH SUCH DEALINGS, WHETHER BASED ON WARRANTY, CONTRACT, TORT, OR ANY OTHER LEGAL THEORY, AND WHETHER OR NOT THE WEBSITE OR ITS SITE OPERATOR ARE ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGES. THE FOREGOING LIMITATION OF LIABILITY SHALL APPLY TO THE FULLEST EXTENT PERMITTED BY LAW IN THE APPLICABLE JURISDICTION.

YOU SPECIFICALLY ACKNOWLEDGE THAT THIS WEBSITE OFFICERS, DIRECTORS, EMPLOYEES, SHALL NOT BE LIABLE FOR CONTENT OR FOR THE DEFAMATORY, OFFENSIVE, OR ILLEGAL CONDUCT OF ANY THIRD PARTY, AND THAT THE RISK OF HARM OR DAMAGE FROM THE FOREGOING RESTS ENTIRELY WITH YOU.

YOU FURTHER ACKNOWLEDGE THAT ANY CONTENT UPLOADED TO THIS WEBSITE MAY BE VIEWED, DOWNLOADED, SHARED, AND DISTRIBUTED – POTENTIALLY IN VIOLATION OF YOUR RIGHTS OR THESE TERMS OF SERVICE AND THAT YOU SOLELY ASSUME SUCH RISKS AS A MATERIAL PART OF THESE TERMS OF SERVICE.

YOU AGREE NOT TO FILE ANY ARBITRATION CLAIM, LAWSUIT OR PROCEEDING INCONSISTENT WITH THE FOREGOING LIABILITY LIMITATIONS.

Any claim by you that may arise in connection with these Terms of Service may be compensable by monetary damages up to, if any, a maximum of your paid subscription fee in the last twelve (12) months, and you will in no event be entitled to injunctive or other equitable relief.

Back to Top

Limitation on Time to File Claims

REGARDLESS OF ANY STATUTE OR LAW TO THE CONTRARY, ANY CAUSE OF ACTION OR CLAIM YOU MAY HAVE ARISING OUT OF OR RELATING TO THESE TERMS OF SERVICE OR THE WEBSITE MUST BE COMMENCED WITHIN ONE (1) YEAR AFTER THE CAUSE OF ACTION ACCRUES, OTHERWISE, SUCH CAUSE OF ACTION OR CLAIM IS PERMANENTLY BARRED.

Back to Top

Notice of Litigation

You shall notify us in writing within two (2) working days after becoming aware of or obtaining knowledge of, any proceedings or threatened proceedings, including any litigation or governmental proceeding pending against you which could materially adversely affect our business, operations, prospects, property, assets, or condition (financial or otherwise); and any other event which is likely to materially adversely affect our business, operations, prospects, property, assets, or condition (financial or otherwise).

Back to Top

Your Comments and Concerns

This Website is operated by Aylo Freesites Ltd, Block 1, 195-197 Old Nicosia-Limassol Road, Dali Industrial Zone, Cyprus 2540. All notices of copyright infringement claims should be sent to the copyright agent designated in our [Copyright Policy](https://www.youporn.com/information/#dmca) in the manner and by the means set forth therein.

All other feedback, comments, requests for technical support and other communications relating to this Website should be directed to: [support@youporn.com](mailto:support@youporn.com).

Back to Top

Assignment

These Terms of Service, and any rights and licenses granted hereunder, may not be transferred, or assigned by you, but may be assigned by us without restriction.

Back to Top

Arbitration Agreement & Waiver of Certain Rights (US)

This section shall only apply to Users located in the United States of America.

Except as set forth hereinabove, you and we agree that we will resolve any disputes between us (including any disputes between you and a third-party agent of ours) through binding and final arbitration instead of through court proceedings. You and we hereby waive any right to a jury trial of any Claim (defined below). All controversies, claims, counterclaims, or other disputes arising between you and us or you and a third-party agent of ours (each a "**Claim**") shall be submitted for binding arbitration in accordance with the Rules of the American Arbitration Association ("**AAA Rules**"). The arbitration will be heard and determined by a single arbitrator. The arbitrator's decision in any such arbitration will be final and binding upon the parties and may be enforced in any court of competent jurisdiction. You and we agree that the arbitration proceedings will be kept confidential and that the existence of the proceeding and any element of it (including, without limitation, any pleadings, briefs or other documents submitted or exchanged and any testimony or other oral submissions and awards) will not be disclosed beyond the arbitration proceedings, except as may lawfully be required in judicial proceedings relating to the arbitration, by applicable disclosure rules and regulations of securities regulatory authorities or other governmental agencies, or as specifically permitted by state law. The Federal Arbitration Act and federal arbitration law apply to this agreement. However, the arbitrator, and not any federal, state, or local court or agency, shall have the exclusive authority to resolve any dispute relating to the interpretation, applicability, enforceability, or formation of these Terms of Service including, but not limited to, a claim that all or any part of these Terms of Service is void or voidable.

If you demonstrate that the costs of arbitration will be prohibitive as compared to the costs of litigation, we will pay as much of the administrative costs and arbitrator's fees required for the arbitration as the arbitrator deems necessary to prevent the cost of the arbitration from being prohibitive. In the final award, the arbitrator may apportion the costs of arbitration and the compensation of the arbitrator among the parties in such amounts as the arbitrator deems appropriate.

This arbitration agreement under this section does not preclude either party from seeking action by federal, state, or local government agencies. You and we also have the right to bring qualifying claims in small claims court. In addition, you and we retain the right to apply to any court of competent jurisdiction for provisional relief, including pre-arbitral attachments or preliminary injunctions, and any such request shall not be deemed incompatible with these Terms of Service, nor a waiver of the right to have disputes submitted to arbitration as provided in these Terms of Service.

Neither you nor we may act as a class representative or private attorney general, nor participate as a member of a class of claimants, with respect to any Claim. Claims may not be arbitrated on a class or representative basis. The arbitrator can decide only your and/or our individual Claims. The arbitrator may not consolidate or join the claims of other persons or parties who may be similarly situated. The arbitrator may award in the arbitration the same damages or other relief available under applicable law, including injunctive and declaratory relief, as if the action were brought in court on an individual basis. Notwithstanding anything to the contrary in the foregoing or herein, the arbitrator may not issue a “public injunction” and any such “public injunction” may be awarded only by a federal or state court. If either party seeks a “public injunction,” all other claims and prayers for relief must be adjudicated in arbitration first and any prayer or claim for a “public injunction” in federal or state court stayed until the arbitration is completed, after which the federal or state court can adjudicate the party’s claim or prayer for “public injunctive relief.” In doing so, the federal or state court is bound under principles of claim or issue preclusion by the decision of the arbitrator.

If any provision of this section is found to be invalid or unenforceable, then that specific provision shall be of no force and effect and shall be severed, but the remainder of this Section shall continue in full force and effect. No waiver of any provision of this section of the Terms of Service will be effective or enforceable unless recorded in a writing signed by the party waiving such a right or requirement. Such a waiver shall not waive or affect any other portion of this Terms of Service. This Section of the Terms will survive the termination of your relationship with us.

THIS SECTION LIMITS CERTAIN RIGHTS, INCLUDING THE RIGHT TO MAINTAIN A COURT ACTION, THE RIGHT TO A JURY TRIAL, THE RIGHT TO PARTICIPATE IN ANY FORM OF CLASS OR REPRESENTATIVE CLAIM, THE RIGHT TO ENGAGE IN DISCOVERY EXCEPT AS PROVIDED IN AAA RULES, AND THE RIGHT TO CERTAIN REMEDIES AND FORMS OF RELIEF. OTHER RIGHTS THAT YOU OR WE WOULD HAVE IN COURT ALSO MAY NOT BE AVAILABLE IN ARBITRATION.

Back to Top

Arbitration Agreement & Waiver of Certain Rights (EU)

This section shall only apply to Users located in the European Union.

We cooperate with out-of-court dispute settlement bodies (“**Dispute Settlement Bodies**”) that have been certified in accordance with Art. 21(3) of the DSA. The European Commission publishes a list of these bodies.

If you have your place of establishment or are located in the European Union, you have the right to select a Dispute Settlement Body to assist in resolving disputes relating to decisions previously taken by us regarding Content uploaded by you, or notices you submitted to us. This includes cases in which complaints have remained unresolved by our internal complaint-handling system, as described in section “Complaint Handling Procedure”.

We reserve the right to refuse to cooperate with your selected Dispute Settlement Body if:

* A dispute has already been resolved or is already subject to an ongoing procedure before a competent court of relevant jurisdiction, or before another Dispute Settlement Body.
* The Dispute Settlement Body has been contacted after the six-month period from notification to you of our decision has lapsed, and you have not previously filed a complaint through our internal complaint-handling system over a particular issue.

Any decisions taken by Dispute Settlement Bodies shall not be binding on either you or us.

We are neither willing nor obligated to participate in dispute resolution proceedings with consumers before a consumer arbitration board under the EU Directive on Consumer ADR.

Miscellaneous

These Terms of Service, your use of this Website, and the relationship between you and us shall be governed by the laws of the Republic of Cyprus, without regard to conflict of law rules. Nothing contained in these Terms of Service shall constitute an agreement to the application of the laws of any other nation to this Website. You agree that this Website shall be deemed a passive Website that does not give rise to personal jurisdiction over us, either specific or general, in jurisdictions other than the Republic of Cyprus. The sole and exclusive jurisdiction and venue for any action or proceeding arising out of or related to these Terms of Service shall be in an appropriate court located in Limassol, Cyprus. You hereby submit to the jurisdiction and venue of said Courts.

No waiver by us of any term or condition set forth in these Terms of Service shall be deemed a further or continuing waiver of such term or condition or a waiver of any other term or condition, and any failure by us to assert a right or provision under these Terms of Service shall not constitute a waiver of such right or provision.

If any provision of these Terms of Service is deemed invalid by a court of competent jurisdiction, the invalidity of such provision shall not affect the validity of the remaining provisions of these Terms of Service, which shall remain in full force and effect.

The Terms of Service, our [Privacy Notice](https://www.youporn.com/information/#privacy), our [Copyright Policy](https://www.youporn.com/information/#dmca) and any documents they expressly incorporate by reference constitute the sole and entire agreement between you and us with respect to this Website.

We may terminate these Terms of Service for any or no reason at any time by notifying you through a notice on this Website, by email, or by any other method of communication. Any such termination will be without prejudice to our rights, remedies, claims, or defenses hereunder. Upon termination of the Terms of Service, you will no longer have a right to access your account or your Content. We will not have any obligation to assist you in migrating your data or your Content and we may not keep any back up of any of your Content. We undertake no responsibility for deleting your Content under these Terms of Service. Note that, even if your Content is deleted from our active servers, it may remain in our archives (but we have no obligation to archive or back-up your Content), and subject to the licenses set forth in these Terms of Service.

Back to Top

Privacy Notice
==============

Last Modified: May 23, 2024

Introduction

Aylo Freesites Ltd (hereinafter “**we**”, “**us**” or “**our**”) operates the website https://www.youporn.com/ (hereinafter "**Youporn**") and is the controller of the information collected or provided via Youporn.

Please read this Privacy Notice carefully, as your access to and use of Youporn signifies that you have read and understand all terms within this Privacy Notice. We respect your privacy and are committed to protecting your personal data.

If you have any questions about our privacy practices, please see the Section “_Contact Information_” below for information on how to contact us.

1\. Scope

For the purposes of this Privacy Notice, “**process**”, “**processed**” or “**processing**” means any operation or set of operations performed on personal data or on sets of personal data (excluding disclosure thereof), whether by automated means, including one or several of the following operations: collection, recording, organization, structuring, storage, adaptation or alteration, retrieval, consultation, use, alignment or combination, restriction, erasure or destruction. Information on disclosure of personal data or of sets of personal data may be found in the “_Disclosure of Your Personal Information_” section below.

This Privacy Notice applies to information we collect:

* on Youporn
    
* and your communications with Youporn via email, online support chats, phoneline support or otherwise;

2\. The Data We Process About You

We may process different kinds of personal data about you, depending on whether you chose to create an account with us.

Persons who visit Youporn without logging in or registering (“**Unregistered Users**”):

* **Contact Data:** We will only process your email address or any other information which you voluntarily provide to us at your direction for a specific function, namely, to participate in a contest or survey.
    
* **Online Forms and Communication Data:** We process Contact Data and other information that you submit through online forms provided on Youporn or information send to us via email, online support chats or such as information provided in the context of support requests or any other inquiries, the content reporting and moderation of content, and our internal complaint handling system.
    
* **Website activity data:** We process information about how you use Youporn and interact with content and advertisements, including the pages you visit on and search history on Youporn, and the referring web page from which you arrived on Youporn from. We process browser and operating system information, devices you use to access Youporn and your time zone setting. We also process online identifiers. Specifically, we process internet protocol (IP) address information and we set cookies as explained below in the section on _Cookies and Automatic Data Collection Technologies_ and as described in our [Cookie Notice](https://www.youporn.com/information/cookie-notice).
    
* **Identifiers:** Some users may be asked to provide identifiers (including government-issued photo identification as well as other documentation) to verify that they are over the age of majority required to have access to Youporn and to view the content. In such cases, this information is processed by trusted third party age verification service providers. This Privacy Notice does not apply to the privacy practices of these third-party age verification service providers. Read the privacy terms and conditions of these third-party service providers carefully.

Persons who choose to create an account on Youporn (“**Registered Users**”): we process the same categories of information described above for Unregistered Users, and additionally the following information:

* **Contact Information:** We process usernames and email addresses. If you choose to register through a third-party platform, we will collect certain personal information from those platforms.
    
* **User Submitted Personal Information:** We process information you submit to personalize your account or for a specific function, for example your date of birth, age, gender, your interests, preferences, feedback, survey responses, your preferences in receiving marketing from us and our third parties, and your communication preferences, as well as any other information which you voluntarily provide to us at your direction for a specific function.
    
* **Identifiers and Biometric Information:** You may be asked to provide identifiers (including government-issued photo identification as well as other documentation) to verify your identity and that you are over the age of majority required to access Youporn and to view the content. We also process biometric information to verify the authenticity of the identifiers you provide us while registering to Youporn, as further explained in the section “_Biometric Information_” below. This information is processed by trusted third party age verification service providers. This Privacy Notice does not apply to the privacy practices of these third-party age verification service providers. Read the privacy terms and conditions of these third party service providers carefully.
    
* **User Contributions including Audio/Video Information:** We provide areas on Youporn where you can post information about yourself and others, communicate with others, upload content (e.g., pictures, video files, etc.), and post comments or reviews of content found on Youporn .

Please use caution in providing user contributions. **By providing user contributions you are making that content and information publicly available.** User contributions can be read, collected, used, and disclosed by others, and we cannot control who accesses your user contributions or what other users may do with the information you voluntarily post or submit. User contributions are governed by the Youporn Terms of Service found at [https://www.youporn.com/information/#terms](https://www.youporn.com/information/#terms).

We may process your data to produce and share aggregated insights that do not directly or indirectly identify you and are not associated with you. Such aggregate information is not personal information.

Youporn is forbidden of access to persons under the age of 18 and the applicable age of majority in the jurisdiction from which Youporn is accessed (“**minors**”), and we therefore prohibit minors from using Youporn. As indicated throughout this Privacy Notice, some users may be asked to provide some information to us and our service providers to verify that you are over the age of majority required to have access to Youporn and to view the content. We do not knowingly process personal information from minors. If you are the parent or legal guardian of a minor who has provided us with personal information, then please contact us at [support@youporn.com](mailto:support@youporn.com) to have that minor’s personal information deleted.

3\. The Sources from Which We Process Personal Information

We process Personal Information in the following ways:

* **Directly from you:** We process the categories of information listed above directly from you.
    
* **Automated technologies or interactions.** As explained in the section below on _"Cookies and Automatic Data Collection Technologies"_, as further described in our [Cookie Notice](https://www.youporn.com/information/cookie-notice), we set cookies and other automatic techniques to process website activity data when you visit Youporn.
    
* **Third-Party Single Sign-on:** We may obtain information if you create or sign-in your account through a third-party platform (such as Google), we will have access to certain information from that platform such as your name, email address or such other information you may have submitted and allowed this third party to share.

4\. Purposes for Which We Process Your Personal Information

We process personal information for the purposes described below.

* **Provision of services:** We process identifiers, website activity data, and, additionally, for Registered Users, Contact Data, and user contributions, including any interactive features on Youporn , and to verify your eligibility and deliver prizes in connection with contests and sweepstakes.
    
* **Customer management (Registered Users Only):** We process identifiers and Contact Data, to manage Registered Users’ account, to provide customer support and notices to the Registered Users about their account, and notices about changes to Youporn or any products or services we offer or provide through them.
    
* **Age and Identity verification:** In some cases, we process identifiers and will use third party service providers to process biometric information for the purpose of verifying your identity and the authenticity of the identifiers you provide to us while registering for an account on Youporn.
    
* **Customization of content and marketing (Unregistered Users and Registered Users):** We process for both Registered Users and Unregistered Users, identifiers and contact information, website activity data; and for Registered Users, user submitted personal information and user contributions to analyze your use of, or interest in, the content, products, or services, to develop and display content and advertising tailored to your interests on Youporn.
    
* **Communications and handling of requests:** We process Online Forms and Communications Data and other information as necessary to respond to and resolve any of your requests, including where this is required to ensure compliance with our legal obligations.
    
* **Analytics:** We process identifiers and website activity data to determine whether users of Youporn are unique, or whether the same user is using Youporn on multiple occasions, and to monitor aggregate metrics such as total number of visitors, pages viewed, demographic patterns.
    
* **Functionality and security:** We may process any of the categories of data we process to diagnose or fix technology problems, and to detect, prevent, and respond to actual or potential fraud, illegal activities, or intellectual property infringement.
    
* **Compliance:** We may process any of the categories of data we process to enforce our Terms of Service and to comply with our legal obligations. In certain jurisdictions, this includes our legal obligation to verify the age of users having access to Youporn.
    
* **Hash Values:** We may create hash values from any of the categories of data we process, such as infringing or illegal content to train our models to detect, prevent, and combat illegal activities including fraud, sexual assault, or exploitation. We reserve the right to share any hashes with law enforcement agencies.
    
* **Information you provide:** We will process contact information and user submitted personal information in any other way we may describe when you provide the information; or for any other purpose with your consent provided separately from this Privacy Notice.

5\. Our Legal Bases Under Canadian and European Union (EU) Privacy Law

To the extent required by applicable law, we rely on several lawful bases to use your data in these ways. This means we process your personal data only where:

* You provide your consent to do so for a specific purpose: for example, when you allow us to show you personalized ads or to send you e-mail marketing.
    
* Biometric information may in some instances also be processed by our third-party service provider based on your consent for identification and age verification purposes. You may withdraw your consent at any time. Withdrawing your consent will not affect the lawfulness of any collection, use, processing, or disclosure that occurred prior to the withdrawal.
    
* It is necessary to perform our contract with you: for example, to create your account and provide our services.
    
* It is necessary to comply with our legal obligations: for example, we may be required to collect, use, or disclose your information in connection with civil, criminal, corporate, taxation, regulatory matters, or litigation.
    
* It satisfies a legitimate interest (which is not overridden by your data protection interests): for example, to keep Youporn safe and secure from fraud and illegal activities.
    
* It is used to protect your or others’ vital interests: for example, in case of emergency or to prevent a crime or fraud.
    
* It is used for tasks carried out in the public interest: for example, to combat unlawful behaviour where it is in the public interest to do so and where the public interest is laid down by applicable law.

Depending on the circumstances, we may rely on different legal bases when processing your same information for different purposes. If you reside outside the European Economic Area (“EEA”), Switzerland or the United Kingdom (“UK”), the legal bases on which we rely may differ from those listed above.

6\. Disclosure of Your Personal Information

We disclose personal information when necessary to perform the services or for other purposes set out in this Privacy Notice. When we disclose your personal information, we usually rely on the performance of our contract with you, our legal obligation to do so, our legitimate interest (e.g., operating Youporn), so long as it doesn’t outweigh your interests or your consent, except when expressly stated otherwise below in the paragraph _"To comply with the law or protect our rights or the rights of third parties"_. Disclosure of your personal information may also involve transfers of your personal information outside the EEA. To the extent that we need to transfer personal information outside the EEA, we will do so according to the section _"Transfers of Your Personal Information to Other Countries"_ or when necessary for the performance of the contract between us. The parties to whom we may disclose your personal information include:

* **the public:** When you submit user contributions including audio/video content, you are using Youporn and services to make that information public.
    
* **our contractors and/or employees:** To provide our services to you, our employees and/or contractors may receive access to your personal data only on a need-to-know basis. Such employees and contractors abide by confidentiality obligations.
    
* **our corporate group:** We may disclose any of the categories of personal information to members of our corporate group to the extent this is necessary for our purposes described in this Privacy Notice, and generally to operate our business, which includes: identification and age verification purposes, transaction monitoring and payment processing, customer support, facilitate business development, administer user accounts or provide IT, technical and engineering support. You acknowledge that in some cases, members of our corporate group might be established or run their services outside the EEA.
    
* **Linked Third-Party Websites or Single Sign-On Services:** You may choose to sign-in, connect or register an account using an external third-party platform, or Single Sign-On (SSO) if available. If you choose to connect your account to a third-party platform, the providers of this platform may receive information about you. When you use third-party platforms, their own terms and privacy policies will govern their use.
    
* **Service providers:** We disclose certain categories of personal information to our authorized service providers that perform certain services on our behalf to enable us to provide our services to you pursuant to our Terms of Service. These service providers may use your information only to perform these tasks on our behalf, may include, identity and document authenticity verification including biometric processing, age verification, risk and fraud detection and mitigation, customer service, marketing and advertising, customization of content, analytics, security, or hosting Youporn or supporting Youporn's functionality. These service providers may only have access to the personal information needed to perform their functions but are not permitted to process such information for any other purposes. Where required under applicable laws, we entered into data processing agreements with such service providers to ensure that personal information is only processed securely within our instructions. You can view the list of our third-party service providers acting as our processors [here](https://www.youporn.com/information/processors).
    
* **Legal successors:** We may disclose the categories of personal information we process to a buyer or other successor in the event of a merger, acquisition or sale or transfer of some or all our assets, whether as a going concern or as part of bankruptcy, liquidation, or similar proceeding. Such transactions may be in our legitimate interest, particularly our interest in making decisions that enable our business to develop.
    
* **To comply with the law or protect our rights or the rights of third parties:** We access, preserve and share all of the categories of personal information with regulators, law enforcement or others where we reasonably believe such disclosure is needed to (a) satisfy any applicable law, regulation, legal process, or governmental request, (b) enforce applicable Terms of Service, including investigation of potential violations thereof, this also includes our Trust and Safety initiative, in the scope of which we may disclose some information to several recipients, (c) detect, prevent, or otherwise address illegal or suspected illegal activities, security, or technical issues, (d) protect against harm to the rights, property or safety of our company, our users, our employees, or others; or (e) to maintain and protect the security and integrity of Youporn or infrastructure. In such cases, we may raise or waive any legal objection or right available to us, in our sole discretion.

For more information on recipients of personal information, please see the section “Contact Information” below on how to contact us.

7\. Cookies and Automatic Data Collection Technologies

As you navigate through and interact with Youporn , we use automatic data collection technologies to collect website activity data. The technologies we use for this automatic data collection may include cookies, which are small text files that are stored in your web browser or downloaded to your device when you visit Youporn . For more information on how we use cookies, please refer to our Cookie Notice, available [here](https://www.youporn.com/information/cookie-notice).

8\. Your Choices About How We Process and Disclose Your Personal Information

We strive to provide you with choices regarding the personal information you provide to us.

* You can choose not to provide us with certain personal information, but that may result in you being unable to use certain features of Youporn because such information may be required for you to register as a member; participate in a contest, promotion, survey, or sweepstakes; ask a question; or initiate other transactions on Youporn.
    
* The Cookie Banner can be utilized to customize your cookie preferences. The Cookie Banner will record when you have consented to our cookies. For logged in users, we will ask for consent once a year or when we have major changes to our cookies, to ensure you stay up to date with changes to our cookies and privacy policies. For non-logged in users, your Cookie Banner selection will be kept only for the specific session. The Cookie Banner specifically controls the Functionality, Analytics, and Advertising cookies set by using Youporn. Strictly necessary cookies cannot be disabled, nor can the tool be used to block cookies on third party websites linked from Youporn.
    
* You can access the Cookie Banner anytime by clicking on the ‘Manage cookies’ option that is located at the footer of Youporn.
    
* You can opt out of receiving marketing emails from us using the opt-out link provided in our emails or by changing your preferences in your account settings. You may use your account settings to delete your user contributions and audio/video information.
    
* You may also delete and deactivate your account with us at any time unless required not to do so by law or by a court order. If you do so, your profile will no longer be accessible by you. If you later choose to have an account with us, you will have to sign up for a new account as none of the information you previously provided or saved within your account will have been saved.
    
* Where we provide you personalised services, we may analyse the information you supply, as well as your activity on Youporn, so that we can offer a more relevant, tailored service. For instance, we could use your favourites' list to provide you with personalised content recommendations or ads. If you don’t want to receive these services, you can switch off the recommendations toggle on the “recommended” page or via the bar at the left of our page. For more information on how we use recommendations, please click [here](https://www.youporn.com/information/#systemguidelines).

9\. California Rights and Choices

As of January 1, 2020, the California Consumer Privacy Act of 2018 (“CCPA”) provides California residents (“Consumer(s)”) certain rights with respect to their personal information, as this term is defined under the CCPA. In addition to the rights that we state under this Privacy Notice, and subject to the exceptions found under the CCPA, Consumers have the right to:

* Opt-out of the sale of their personal information, should we sell their personal information;
    
* Be informed of certain information concerning our collection and use of their personal information;
    
* Request that we delete certain personal information we collected from them;
    
* Appoint an agent to exercise their rights provided for by the CCPA, provided that a duly executed notarized power of attorney is presented and provided that the agent has information deemed sufficient to allow us to verify the identity of the Consumer in question and to locate his/her information in our systems;
    
* Not be subjected to discrimination for the exercise of these rights. We will not deny California residents the use of our service, neither will we provide a different level or quality or services for exercising any of their CCPA rights, unless as permitted under the CCPA.

Youporn does not sell, nor has it sold in the past twelve (12) months personal information to third parties for monetary or other valuable consideration. We may however disclose certain personal information with third parties, service providers and entities within our corporate group to enable them to perform certain services on our behalf and namely to make Youporn work properly, as described in the section above titled _Disclosure of Your Personal Information_.

Regardless, we respect the California residents’ right to exclude personal information from such sharing arrangements and to thereby opt-out of any future sale of their personal information. If the CCPA is applicable to you and you would like to exercise your rights, please use the buttons at the bottom of this page or email us at [support@youporn.com](mailto:support@youporn.com) with the email subject line “CCPA Request.”

In either case you will need to provide the following information to verify your identity and enable us to locate your information in our systems: your username and email address that you used to create an account with us, as well as any other information which we may reasonably request for us to verify your identity. We may require you verify that you have access to your account and/or email account that you used to register with us.

You can designate an agent to make a request by executing a notarized power of attorney to have that person act on your behalf and providing that person with the information listed above that allows us to verify your identity and locate your information. Alternatively, you will need to directly confirm your identity with us using the methods described above, sign an authorization for the agent to act on your behalf and provide us with confirmation that you have done so.

10\. Resident’s Rights – Jurisdictions in the United States, Where Applicable

We do not sell, trade, or exchange the Registered Users’ personal information with anyone for money.

11\. Biometric Information

We employ third-party service providers to verify your identity, age, and the authenticity of the identification documents you provide using facial recognition technology. Facial recognition technology creates a mathematical representation of your facial features from the live scan of your face, your selfie, and the government-issued ID you submit or previously submitted to us. Information derived from this mathematical representation, which may be considered biometric information under the laws of certain states and countries, is shared by our service providers with us as further described below.

Your biometric information will be processed to:

* verify you are a real, live person and to prevent the use of methods which would allow a user to identify as someone else;
    
* to match your selfie with your government-issued ID you submit or previously submitted to us to make sure that nobody is impersonating you;
    
* to help confirm your age;

Please note that this section entitled _"Biometric Information"_ applies to relevant users who wish to upload content onto Youporn but does not apply to identifiers processed by our third-party age verification service providers solely for the purpose of granting you access to Youporn. Our third-party service providers will store your biometric information according to their retention policies, please consult the section _"Retention of Personal Information"_ below to understand our retention practices.

12\. Notice to Law Enforcement

The following information serves as a guideline for law enforcement officials seeking disclosure of records. You may serve us a valid court order, subpoena, search warrant or equivalent legal or official administrative document by respecting the following conditions:

1. The document(s) is uploaded, and all required fields have been filed out adequately on our platform for Legal Service Process located at: [https://legalservice.aylo.com/legal/datarequest](https://legalservice.aylo.com/legal/datarequest);
    
2. The document(s) you are serving is correctly issued to Aylo Freesites Ltd by a valid Court of Law or equivalent legal or administrative authority to us;
    
3. The document(s) is also sent by mail at the following address: 195-197 Old Nicosia-Limassol Road, Block 1 Dali Industrial Zone, Cyprus 2540.

We reserve the right to refuse online service through Youporn, namely in cases where the above requirements are not met and require formal legal service at the above address. In such an event, you will be notified. We may raise or waive any legal objection or right available, in our sole discretion.

13\. Transfers of Your Personal Information to Other Countries

By using Youporn you consent to the transfer of information that we process about you, which may include personal information to other countries in which members of our corporate group or our service providers are located. When we transfer personal information to countries outside of the EEA or other regions or countries with comprehensive data protection laws, we will ensure that the information is transferred in accordance with the applicable laws. Where applicable, we rely on decisions of the European Commission, known as “adequacy decisions”, recognizing that certain countries offer a level of protection of personal data that is essentially equivalent to the EEA. In other situations, we rely on standard contractual clauses approved by the European Commission (and the equivalent standard contractual clauses for the UK, where appropriate) or on derogations provided for under the applicable law to transfer information to a third country.

For more information or to obtain a copy of our standard contractual clauses, please see the section “_Contact Information_” below on how to contact us.

14\. Retention of Personal Information

We will only retain your personal information for as long as your account is active, or for as long as necessary to fulfil the purposes we processed it for, including for the purposes of satisfying any legal, accounting, or reporting requirements.

To determine the appropriate retention period for personal data, we consider several factors, including what personal data we are processing, the risk of harm from any unauthorised disclosure, why we are processing your personal data and whether we can achieve this outcome by another means without having to process it.

Where we no longer need to process your personal information for the purposes set out in this Privacy Notice, we will delete your personal information from our systems.

For more information on data retention periods, please contact us by using the information in the Section _"Contact Information"_ below.

Where permissible, we will also delete your personal information upon your request as explained in the section _"Your Rights Related to Your Personal Information"_.

15\. Third-Party Links and Sites

If you click on a link to a third-party website, you will be taken to websites we do not control. This Privacy Notice does not apply to the privacy practices of these websites. Read the Privacy Notice of other websites carefully. We are not responsible for these third-party practices.

16\. Changes to Our Privacy Notice

We may modify or revise our Privacy Notice from time to time. If we change anything in our Privacy Notice, the date of change will be reflected in the “last modified date”. We may attempt to notify you of any material changes as required by law. Please also periodically review the most up-to-date version of our Privacy Notice, which will be posted at this location, so you are aware of any changes.

17\. Contact Information

If you have any questions about this Privacy Notice or our information-handling practices, please contact us at [support@youporn.com](mailto:support@youporn.com).

You may also contact us at 195-197 Old Nicosia-Limassol Road, Block 1 Dali Industrial Zone, Cyprus 2540, Phone: +357 22662 320, Fax: +357 22343 282.

Our Data Protection Officer can be contacted at the following email address: [dpo@youporn.com](mailto:dpo@youporn.com).

18\. Your Rights Related to Your Personal Information

Subject to local law and applicable legal requirements and exemptions, you have certain rights regarding your personal data:

* **Right of access**: you have the right to receive information on the personal data we hold about you and how such personal data is used, as well as a copy of your personal data;
    
* **Right to rectification**: you have the right to rectify inaccurate personal data concerning you;
    
* **Right to be forgotten**: you have the right to delete/erase your personal data;
    
* **Right to data portability**: you have the right to receive the personal data provided by you in a structured, commonly used, and machine-readable format and to transmit this personal data to another data controller;
    
* **Right to object**: you have the right to object to the use of your personal data where such use is based on our legitimate interests or on public interests;
    
* **Right to restriction of processing**: you have the right in some cases, to restrict our use of your personal data.
    
* **Right to file a complaint**: If you are in the EEA or the UK, you also have a right to lodge a complaint with your local data protection authority.

If we ask for your consent to process your personal data, you have the right to withdraw your consent at any time. Note that, in that case, you may no longer able to use several functionalities of Youporn or access Youporn in some cases.

You can exercise your rights of access or deletion of your data by following the dedicated links in the section “Manage My Data” below. If you need assistance regarding the exercise of your rights, you can also send an e-mail at [support@youporn.com](mailto:support@youporn.com) to help you with the process. Please note that we have one month to respond to your request.

Prior to processing an access or deletion request, we will need to verify your identity and ensure your right to access or delete the information. This is an appropriate and reasonable security measure to ensure that personal data is not disclosed to any person who has no right to receive it or deleted in an unauthorized way.

Please note that unless you have created an account with us, we may not have sufficient information to identify you and therefore may not be able to respond to your request. Additionally, in some cases to adequately verify your identity or your authorization to make the request, we may require you to provide additional information.

Note that some requests to delete certain personal information will require the deletion of your user account as the provision of user accounts are inextricably linked to the processing of certain personal information (e.g., your e-mail address). If you delete your account, your personal data and all account related information including, but not limited to, user profile data, sharing data and any data or content specifically associated with your account will no longer be accessible by you. If, after deleting your account, you wish to have an account with us in the future, you will have to sign up for a new account.

19\. Manage My Data

Registered Users may request a copy of their personal data or request the deletion of their personal data via the links below. Please note that the below website is governed by the present Privacy Notice.

_Note: AdBlocker add-ons interfere with the Manage My Data system. Please disable them._

RTA
===

Youporn is rated with RTA label. Parents, you can easily block access to this site. Please read this page [http://www.rtalabel.org/index.php?content=parents](http://www.rtalabel.org/index.php?content=parents) for more information.

Advertise on Youporn
====================

Name:\* 

E-mail:\* 

Subject: 

My site: 

I'm interested in: Global Traffic Geo-targeted Traffic

Comments:\*

Send

Success!
--------

Your inquiry has been sent successfully. Youporn Support will respond to your inquiry as soon as possible.

Start advertising on Youporn today
----------------------------------

#### Success

Your inquiry has been sent successfully. Youporn support will respond to your inqury as soon as possible.

OK

#### Error

An error happened while submitting your request. Please try again later or contact customer support. Thank you.

OK

COPYRIGHT POLICY
================

Last Modified: August 17, 2023

Reporting Claims of Copyright Infringement

We take claims of copyright infringement seriously. We will respond to notices of alleged copyright infringement that comply with the Digital Millennium Copyright Act (the **“DMCA”**) or any other applicable intellectual property legislation or laws. Responses may include removing, blocking or disabling access to material claimed to be the subject of infringing activity, terminating the user’s access to [Youporn.com](https://www.youporn.com/) (“**Youporn**”), or all of the foregoing.

If you believe any material accessible on Youporn infringes your copyright, you may submit a copyright infringement notification (see below, “Filing a DMCA Notice of Copyright Infringement” for instructions on filing such a notice). These requests should only be submitted by the copyright owner or an agent authorized to act on the owner’s behalf.

If we remove or disable access to material in response to such a notice, we will take reasonable steps to notify the user that uploaded the affected content material that we have removed or disabled access to so that the user has the opportunity to submit a counter notification (see below, “Counter-Notification Procedures” for instructions on filing a counter notification). It is our policy to document all notices of alleged infringement on which we act.

All copyright infringement notifications and counter-notifications must be written in English. Any attempted notifications written in foreign languages or using foreign characters may, at our discretion, be deemed non-compliant and disregarded.

Filing a DMCA Notice of Copyright Infringement

If you choose to request removal of content by submitting an infringement notification, please remember that you are initiating a legal process. Do not make false claims. Misuse of this process may result in the suspension of your account or other legal consequences.

You may notify Youporn of alleged copyright infringement via our form found at [/information/#dmcaForm](https://www.youporn.com/information/#dmcaForm). This form is designed to help you identify your content accurately and help speed up the process of content take-down.

In accordance with the DMCA, the written notice (the **“DMCA Notice”**) must include substantially the following:

* Identification of the copyrighted work you believe to have been infringed or, if the claim involves multiple works, a representative list of such works.
* Identification of the material you believe to be infringing in a sufficiently precise manner to allow us to locate that material. If your complaint does not contain the specific URL of the video you believe infringes your rights, we may be unable to locate and remove it. General information about the video, such as a channel URL or username, is typically not adequate. Please include the URL(s) of the exact video(s).
* Adequate information by which we, and the uploader(s) of any video(s) you remove, can contact you (including your name, postal address, telephone number and, if available, e-mail address).
* A statement that you have a good faith belief that use of the copyrighted material is not authorized by the copyright owner, its agent or the law.
* A statement that the information in the written notice is accurate, and under penalty of perjury, that you are the owner, or an agent authorized to act on behalf of the owner, of an exclusive right that is allegedly infringed.
* Complete complaints require the physical or electronic signature of the copyright owner or a representative authorized to act on their behalf. To satisfy this requirement, you may type your full legal name to act as your signature at the bottom of your complaint.

Our designated Copyright Agent to receive DMCA Notices is:

Lawrence G. Walters  
**Walters Law Group**  
195 W. Pine Ave.  
Longwood, FL 32750  
Email: copyright@aylofreesites.com  

Please do not send other inquiries or requests to our designated copyright agent. Absent prior express permission, our designated copyright agent is not authorized to accept or waive service of formal legal process, and any agency relationship beyond that required to receive valid DMCA Notices or Counter-Notices (as defined below) is expressly disclaimed.

If you fail to comply with all of the requirements of Section 512(c)(3) of the DMCA, your DMCA Notice may not be effective.

Please be aware that if you knowingly materially misrepresent that material or activity on Youporn is infringing your copyright, you may be held liable for damages (including costs and attorneys’ fees) under Section 512(f) of the DMCA.

The copyright owner’s name will be published on Youporn in place of disabled content. This will become part of the public record of your DMCA Notice, along with your description of the work(s) allegedly infringed. All the information provided in a DMCA Notice, the actual DMCA Notice (including your personal information), or both may be forwarded to the uploader of the allegedly infringing content. By submitting a DMCA Notice, you consent to having your information revealed in this way.

Counter-Notification Procedures

If you have received a DMCA Notice and believe that material you posted on Youporn was removed or access to it was disabled by mistake or misidentification, you may file a counter-notification with us (a “Counter-Notice”). Counter notifications must be submitted by the video’s original uploader or an agent authorized to act on their behalf.

Counter-notices must be sent to our designated agent:

Lawrence G. Walters  
**Walters Law Group**  
195 W. Pine Ave.  
Longwood, FL 32750  
Email: copyright@aylofreesites.com  

Please do not send other inquiries or requests to our designated copyright agent. Absent prior express permission, our designated copyright agent is not authorized to accept or waive service of formal legal process, and any agency relationship beyond that required to receive valid DMCA Notices or Counter-Notices is expressly disclaimed.

Pursuant to the DMCA, the Counter-Notice must include substantially the following:

* Your name, address, phone number and physical or electronic signature;
* Identification of the allegedly infringing content and its location before removal or access to it was disabled;
* A statement under penalty of perjury that you believe in good faith that the content was removed by mistake or misidentification; and
* A statement that you consent to the jurisdiction of the U.S. Federal District Court for the judicial district in which you are located (or if you are outside the U.S., for any judicial district in which the operator of Youporn may be found), and that you will accept service of process from the person who originally provided us with the DMCA Notice or an agent of such person.

We will not respond to Counter-Notices that do not meet the requirements set out above.

After we receive your Counter Notice, we will forward it to the party who submitted the original DMCA Notice and inform that party that the removed material may be restored after ten (10) business days but no later than fourteen (14) business days from the date we received your Counter Notice, unless our Designated Agent first receives notice from the party who filed the original DMCA Notice informing us that such party has filed a court action to restrain you from engaging in infringing activity related to the material in question.

Please note that when we forward your Counter Notice, it will include your personal information. By submitting a counter notification, you consent to having your information revealed in this way. We will not forward the counter notification to any party other than the original claimant or to law enforcement or parties that assist us with enforcing and protecting our rights.

Please be aware that if you knowingly materially misrepresent that material or activity on Youporn was removed or disabled by mistake or misidentification, you may be held liable for damages (including costs and attorneys’ fees) under Section 512(f) of the DMCA.

Back to Top

Repeat Infringers

In accordance with the DMCA and other applicable law, we have adopted a policy of terminating or disabling, in appropriate circumstances and at our sole discretion, the accounts of users who are deemed to be repeat infringers. We may also at our sole discretion limit access to Youporn, terminate or disable the accounts of any users who infringe any intellectual property rights of others, whether or not there is any repeat infringement.

Back to Top

Video Fingerprinting

We use MediaWise®, an automated audiovisual identification system, to assist us in identifying and blocking potentially infringing content from being uploaded by users. Videos uploaded to Youporn are compared against a database of digital fingerprints. When a video is matched to a digital fingerprint, access to it is disabled.

If you are interested in having your content digitally fingerprinted by the provider of the automated audiovisual identification system we use, please contact Vobile in one of the manners described at [https://us.vobile.com/contact](https://us.vobile.com/contact).

Back to Top

2257
====

**18 U.S.C. §2257 Record Keeping Requirements Compliance Statement.**

The operator of Youporn is not the producer (whether primary or secondary as defined in 18 U.S.C. § 2257) of any of the content found on Youporn. The operator’s activities, with respect to such content, are limited to the transmission, storage, retrieval, hosting and/or formatting of depictions posted by third party users, on areas of the website under the user's control.

Please direct any request you may have regarding §2257 records in relation to any content found on Youporn, directly to the respective uploader, amateur, producer, studio or account holder of the content (**"Verified Uploaders"**).

For further assistance in communicating with the Verified Uploaders or any questions regarding this notice, please contact Youporn’s compliance department at [support@youporn.com](mailto:support@youporn.com).

Youporn abides by the following strict compliance procedures regarding uploaded content:

* All Verified Uploaders must be over eighteen (18) years of age (or age required by their State, jurisdiction or Country if more than 18 years old) and are personally identified and verified by Youporn at account activation prior to being able to upload, share and sell content on Youporn;
* Prior to uploads, Youporn ensures that all Verified Uploaders, provide evidence or certify that:
    * all individuals appearing in the content are over the age of 18 years old (or minimal age required to appear in such content by their State, jurisdiction or Country if more than 18 years old); that they freely consented to appear in the content at the time of its production and agree to its upload on Youporn;
    * as producer of said content, the Verified Uploader certifies being compliant with record keeping requirements under U.S.C. § 2257 for all content uploaded on Youporn, and agrees to deliver such documentation promptly upon request;
    * the uploaded content does not violate Youporn’s [Terms of Service](https://www.youporn.com/information/#terms), and any of its related policies namely but without limitation, its [Child Sexual Abuse Material Policy](https://help.pornhub.com/hc/en-us/articles/360041234774-Child-Sexual-Abuse-Material-Policy), or [Non-Consensual Content Policy](https://help.pornhub.com/hc/en-us/articles/360041719433-Non-Consensual-Content-Policy).

Contact Us
==========

Select a Category General Support/Technical Support Request Login Information Request Video be Removed Cancel Free Account Cancel Premium Account Premium/HD Services Broken Link Chat Mobile Video Streaming Video Download Video Upload Inappropriate Content Content Partner Program & Advertisers Suggestions (Feedback/Comments) Report Issues with Ads Media Inquiries

Email Address\* 

Username 

Subject\* 

Message\*

Screenshot picture 

For any content removal requests please use our [content removal form](https://www.youporn.com/content-removal).

Send

Success!
--------

Your inquiry has been sent successfully. Youporn Support will respond to your inquiry as soon as possible..

Have you checked the FAQs?
--------------------------

Hold your horses, Jack! Before you go submitting a support ticket, check out the [Frequently Asked Questions (FAQs)](https://www.youporn.com/information/#faq) section.If you've already been there, done that, and come up empty handed, then fill out the support form below and we'll do our best to help you out.

Success!

Your inquiry has been sent successfully. Youporn Support will respond to your inquiry as soon as possible.

Ok

FAQ
===

General Account Management Account Settings Video / Upload Management Site Features Advertisers & Content Partners Other

What is Youporn?

If you haven't figured it out by now, it's shocking that you've made it this far. Youporn is a 100% free streaming adult video site hosting hundreds of thousands of videos from every genre imaginable that services more than 15 million visitors worldwide every day.

I want to make sure a video of me or my content never gets uploaded to Youporn / the Pornhub Network.

You can find more information on how to remove content by visiting [content removal form](https://www.youporn.com/content-removal)

We use MediaWise®, a third-party automated audiovisual identification system, to assist us in identifying and blocking potentially infringing content from being uploaded by users. Videos uploaded to Pornhub are compared against MediaWise®’s database of digital fingerprints. When a video is matched to a digital fingerprint, access to it is disabled. If you are interested in having your content digitally fingerprinted by the provider of the automated audiovisual identification system we use, please contact Vobile in one of the manners described at [https://us.vobile.com/contact](https://us.vobile.com/contact)

Where do I sign up?

Signing up for a Youporn.com account is fast, easy, and free, and gives you access to special features only registered users can use. To sign up for an account, go to [www.youporn.com/register/](https://www.youporn.com/register/), fill out and submit the form, and then check your email for a verification link. If you don't receive the link within 1 hour, don't panic; check your Spam/Junk Mail folder as it may have found its way in there by mistake.

I signed up but never received an activation email, what do I do now?

Don't worry, take a deep breath, we'll get through this together. Your first stop should be checking your Spam/Junk mail folder to see if it ended up in there by mistake. If you don't find it there, it's been over an hour, and you still haven't received your verification email, then contact Youporn Support using the form at [https://www.youporn.com/information/#support](https://www.youporn.com/information/#support) and we'll get you squared away in no time.

Help! I forgot my password, how can I retrieve it?

Retrieving your password is simple: Just go to [www.youporn.com/login/forgotpassword/](https://www.youporn.com/login/forgotpassword/), enter the email address you signed up with, and check your email for instructions. Don't forget to check your Spam/Junk folder if you don't see the email within 1 hour.

I forgot my password and signed up before 2012, what now?

Not to worry, we can help with that too. Contact support using the form at [https://www.youporn.com/information/#support](#support) (be sure to include your username) and we'll get you reconnected with your long lost account in no time.

Uh oh, I forgot my username, how can I retrieve it?

If you signed up after 2012 and provided an email address during the sign-up process, then contact support using the form at [https://www.youporn.com/information/#support](https://www.youporn.com/information/#support) (be sure to include the email address) and we'll send you your username. If your account was created before 2012, and doesn't have an email address associated with it, we won't be able to retrieve your username - sorry, we're not mind readers. You can, however, sign up for a new account without a problem (see: Where do I sign up?).

Can I change my password? \*

You can change your password at any time. To do so, click on your username in the top right corner of the site, select "Settings" from the drop-down menu, and then click "Change password" in the left hand menu. Fill out the form, hit save, and you're good to go.

Where do I update my email address? \*

If you've changed email addresses, or signed up before 2012 and never had one associated with your account, click on your username in the top right corner of the site, select "Settings" from the drop-down menu, and then click "Edit/add email" in the left hand menu. Fill out the form, hit save, and you're email address will be updated.

_\* Note: you must be logged in to an existing Youporn.com account to complete these actions._

How do I upload a video? \*

Only content partners and people within the Model Program are able to upload content to Youporn.

How do I delete the video(s) I uploaded?

Don't want your video on the site anymore? No problem. Just contact support at [https://www.youporn.com/information/#support](https://www.youporn.com/information/#support) with the URL of the video(s) you would like removed and they should be taken down within 24-48hrs.

The videos won't stream, what's wrong?

If you're having trouble getting videos to play, try clearing your browser's cache and cookies, then refreshing the page. If that doesn't do the trick, contact Youporn support at [https://www.youporn.com/information/#support](https://www.youporn.com/information/#support) and we'll do our best to help you out.

_\* Note: you must be logged in to an existing Youporn.com account to complete these actions._

How do I add a video to my Favorites? \*

Any video on Youporn.com can be added to Your Favorites simply by clicking the heart shaped button below the video. You can also add a video to Your Favorites from any non-video player page by tapping the 'i' icon under the thumbnail and tapping the heart icon "Add to Favorites".

Can I remove a video from my Favorites? \*

Don't need that video in your favorites anymore? No problem. To remove a video from Your Favorites, just click on your username in the top right corner of the site (or go to [www.youporn.com/favorites/](https://www.youporn.com/favorites/)), select "Favorites" from the menu, and click the "X" above the top left corner of the video you want to remove from Your Favorites.

Where can I make a Collection? \*

**All other pages:**  
Making a collection is easy. Find a video you'd like to include in your collection, tap the 'i' icon under the thumbnail, tap the folder icon 'Add to Collection...' and click on 'New Collection' at the bottom of the dialog. Enter a title for your new collection, click save, and a new collection will be created with that video in it.

**Video Page:**  
To create a new collection from a video page, click the '+' icon below the video, go to 'Add to Collection...' and click on 'New Collection' at the bottom of the dialog, enter a title for your new collection, click save, and a new collection will be created with that video in it.

How can I add a video to my Collections? \*

To add a new video to an existing collection from any non-video player page, tap the 'i' icon under the thumbnail, tap the folder icon 'Add to Collection...' and click on the title of the existing collection you'd like to add the video to.

To add a new video to an existing collection from any video player page, just click the 'Add to Collection' button below the video and select the existing collection you'd like to add the video to.

Can I create a Channel?

At this time Channel pages are only available to Youporn Content Partners. If you run an adult website and would like to become a Content Partner, please visit [www.youporn.com/contentpartnerprogram/](https://www.youporn.com/contentpartnerprogram/) .

How do I subscribe to a Channel/Pornstar? \*

To subscribe to a Channel, you can go to [www.youporn.com/channels/](https://www.youporn.com/channels/), search for the Channel you want, and then click the "Subscribe" button next to the channel name in the top right corner of the page, or if you're on a video player page, just click the "Subscribe" button next to the "By: Channel Name" below the video.

To subscribe to a Pornstar, go to [www.youporn.com/pornstars/](https://www.youporn.com/pornstars/), select the pornstar you wish to subscribe to, and click the "Subscribe" button below their picture on the left side of the page.

Where can I find my subscriptions? \*

All of your subscriptions can be viewed, filtered, and managed from Your Subscriptions page. To access the page, click on your username in the top right corner of the site and select "Subscriptions" from the drop-down menu (or go to [www.youporn.com/subscriptions/](https://www.youporn.com/subscriptions/)).

How do I unsubscribe from a Channel/Pornstar? \*

To unsubscribe from a Channel, Pornstar click on your username in the top right corner of the site, select "Subscriptions" from the drop-down menu, select the Channel, Pornstar you would like to unsubscribe from under the subscriptions list on the left side of the page, then click on the "Unsubscribe" button to the right of the page above the list of videos.

You can also unsubscribe from Channels, Pornstars by simply clicking the "Unsubscribe" button found on any Channel, Pornstar.

_\* Note: you must be logged in to an existing Youporn.com account to complete these actions._

I'd like to buy an Ad on Youporn, how does that work?

All ads on Youporn.com are managed by Traffic Junky. For information on how to contact Traffic Junky, see [https://www.youporn.com/information/#advertise](https://www.youporn.com/information/#advertise).

I run an adult website, do you have an affiliate/partner program?

If you run your own adult website, produce your own xxx videos, and would like to promote your content on Youporn.com, visit the Youporn Content Partner page at [www.youporn.com/contentpartnerprogram/](https://www.youporn.com/contentpartnerprogram/) for more information.

Can I embed Youporn.com videos on my site?

Absolutely. To embed a single video on your website, simply click the "Embed" button below any video, copy the provided code from the pop-up, and paste the code into your site.

I've a great idea to make Youporn.com better, where can I send it?

Great ideas can come from anywhere, and Youporn users have the best! If you've got an idea of how to make Youporn.com better, please submit it for consideration on the Youporn [contact form](https://www.youporn.com/information/#support).

Does Youporn.com have any social media accounts I can follow?

You can find us on Twitter at [https://twitter.com/youporn](https://twitter.com/youporn).

I'm a member of the media, who can I contact with questions?

Yes, please refer to the [Support page](https://www.youporn.com/information/#support) and select the ‘Media Inquiry' category.

My question wasn't answered here, what can I do now?

If you couldn't find the answers you were looking for here, feel free to contact Youporn support at any time via [https://www.youporn.com/information/#support](https://www.youporn.com/information/#support).

DMCA Takedown Form
==================

Content To Be Removed
---------------------

Location (URL) of the allegedly infringing work or material: 

Location (URL) of the work or material being infringed: 

Description of the work claimed to be infringed: Please Choose My or my company's, organization's or client's video My or my company's, organization's or client's photo My or my company's, organization's or client's original music or song My or my company's, organization's or client's software My or my company's, organization's or client's artwork Other

Title of original video: 

Title of original photo: 

Title of original music or song: 

Title of software: 

Title of artwork: 

Type of copyrighted work:  Title of copyrighted work: 

Incident ID: 

Location (URL) of the allegedly infringing work or material: 

Location (URL) of the work or material being infringed: 

Description of the work claimed to be infringed: Please Choose My or my company's, organization's or client's video My or my company's, organization's or client's photo My or my company's, organization's or client's original music or song My or my company's, organization's or client's software My or my company's, organization's or client's artwork Other

Title of original video: 

Title of original photo: 

Title of original music or song: 

Title of software: 

Title of artwork: 

Type of copyrighted work:  Title of copyrighted work: 

Incident ID: 

Location (URL) of the allegedly infringing work or material: 

Location (URL) of the work or material being infringed: 

Description of the work claimed to be infringed: Please Choose My or my company's, organization's or client's video My or my company's, organization's or client's photo My or my company's, organization's or client's original music or song My or my company's, organization's or client's software My or my company's, organization's or client's artwork Other

Title of original video: 

Title of original photo: 

Title of original music or song: 

Title of software: 

Title of artwork: 

Type of copyrighted work:  Title of copyrighted work: 

Incident ID: 

Location (URL) of the allegedly infringing work or material: 

Location (URL) of the work or material being infringed: 

Description of the work claimed to be infringed: Please Choose My or my company's, organization's or client's video My or my company's, organization's or client's photo My or my company's, organization's or client's original music or song My or my company's, organization's or client's software My or my company's, organization's or client's artwork Other

Title of original video: 

Title of original photo: 

Title of original music or song: 

Title of software: 

Title of artwork: 

Type of copyrighted work:  Title of copyrighted work: 

Incident ID: 

Location (URL) of the allegedly infringing work or material: 

Location (URL) of the work or material being infringed: 

Description of the work claimed to be infringed: Please Choose My or my company's, organization's or client's video My or my company's, organization's or client's photo My or my company's, organization's or client's original music or song My or my company's, organization's or client's software My or my company's, organization's or client's artwork Other

Title of original video: 

Title of original photo: 

Title of original music or song: 

Title of software: 

Title of artwork: 

Type of copyrighted work:  Title of copyrighted work: 

Incident ID: 

Location (URL) of the allegedly infringing work or material: 

Location (URL) of the work or material being infringed: 

Description of the work claimed to be infringed: Please Choose My or my company's, organization's or client's video My or my company's, organization's or client's photo My or my company's, organization's or client's original music or song My or my company's, organization's or client's software My or my company's, organization's or client's artwork Other

Title of original video: 

Title of original photo: 

Title of original music or song: 

Title of software: 

Title of artwork: 

Type of copyrighted work:  Title of copyrighted work: 

Incident ID: 

Location (URL) of the allegedly infringing work or material: 

Location (URL) of the work or material being infringed: 

Description of the work claimed to be infringed: Please Choose My or my company's, organization's or client's video My or my company's, organization's or client's photo My or my company's, organization's or client's original music or song My or my company's, organization's or client's software My or my company's, organization's or client's artwork Other

Title of original video: 

Title of original photo: 

Title of original music or song: 

Title of software: 

Title of artwork: 

Type of copyrighted work:  Title of copyrighted work: 

Incident ID: 

Location (URL) of the allegedly infringing work or material: 

Location (URL) of the work or material being infringed: 

Description of the work claimed to be infringed: Please Choose My or my company's, organization's or client's video My or my company's, organization's or client's photo My or my company's, organization's or client's original music or song My or my company's, organization's or client's software My or my company's, organization's or client's artwork Other

Title of original video: 

Title of original photo: 

Title of original music or song: 

Title of software: 

Title of artwork: 

Type of copyrighted work:  Title of copyrighted work: 

Incident ID: 

Location (URL) of the allegedly infringing work or material: 

Location (URL) of the work or material being infringed: 

Description of the work claimed to be infringed: Please Choose My or my company's, organization's or client's video My or my company's, organization's or client's photo My or my company's, organization's or client's original music or song My or my company's, organization's or client's software My or my company's, organization's or client's artwork Other

Title of original video: 

Title of original photo: 

Title of original music or song: 

Title of software: 

Title of artwork: 

Type of copyrighted work:  Title of copyrighted work: 

Incident ID: 

Location (URL) of the allegedly infringing work or material: 

Location (URL) of the work or material being infringed: 

Description of the work claimed to be infringed: Please Choose My or my company's, organization's or client's video My or my company's, organization's or client's photo My or my company's, organization's or client's original music or song My or my company's, organization's or client's software My or my company's, organization's or client's artwork Other

Title of original video: 

Title of original photo: 

Title of original music or song: 

Title of software: 

Title of artwork: 

Type of copyrighted work:  Title of copyrighted work: 

Incident ID: 

Add content first before choosing to add another.

\+ Add another content

Contact Information
-------------------

First Name: 

Last Name: 

Email Address: 

Phone Number: 

Copyright holder name (ex: company or full legal name): 

Address: 

City: 

State/Region/Province: 

Country: Select Afghanistan Aland Islands Albania Algeria American Samoa Andorra Angola Anguilla Antarctica Antigua and Barbuda Argentina Armenia Aruba Asia/Pacific Region Australia Austria Azerbaijan Bahamas Bahrain Bangladesh Barbados Belarus Belgium Belize Benin Bermuda Bhutan Bolivia Bosnia and Herzegovina Botswana Bouvet Island Brazil British Indian Ocean Territory Brunei Darussalam Bulgaria Burkina Faso Burundi Cambodia Cameroon Canada Cape Verde Cayman Islands Central African Republic Chad Chile China Christmas Island Cocos (Keeling) Islands Colombia Comoros Congo Congo, The Democratic Republic of the Cook Islands Costa Rica Cote D'Ivoire Croatia Cuba Cyprus Czech Republic Denmark Djibouti Dominica Dominican Republic Ecuador Egypt El Salvador Equatorial Guinea Eritrea Estonia Ethiopia Europe Falkland Islands (Malvinas) Faroe Islands Fiji Finland France French Guiana French Polynesia French Southern Territories Gabon Gambia Georgia Germany Ghana Gibraltar Greece Greenland Grenada Guadeloupe Guam Guatemala Guernsey Guinea Guinea-Bissau Guyana Haiti Heard Island and McDonald Islands Holy See (Vatican City State) Honduras Hong Kong Hungary Iceland India Indonesia Iran => Islamic Republic of Iraq Ireland Isle of Man Israel Italy Jamaica Japan Jersey Jordan Kazakhstan Kenya Kiribati Korea, Democratic People's Republic of Korea, Republic of Kuwait Kyrgyzstan Lao People's Democratic Republic Latvia Lebanon Lesotho Liberia Libyan Arab Jamahiriya Liechtenstein Lithuania Luxembourg Macau Macedonia Madagascar Malawi Malaysia Maldives Mali Malta Marshall Islands Martinique Mauritania Mauritius Mayotte Mexico Micronesia, Federated States of Moldova, Republic of Monaco Mongolia Montenegro Montserrat Morocco Mozambique Myanmar Namibia Nauru Nepal Netherlands Netherlands Antilles New Caledonia New Zealand Nicaragua Niger Nigeria Niue Norfolk Island Northern Mariana Islands Norway Oman Pakistan Palau Palestinian Territory, Occupied Panama Papua New Guinea Paraguay Peru Philippines Pitcairn Islands Poland Portugal Puerto Rico Qatar Reunion Romania Russian Federation Rwanda Saint Barthelemy Saint Helena Saint Kitts and Nevis Saint Lucia Saint Martin Saint Pierre and Miquelon Saint Vincent and the Grenadines Samoa San Marino Sao Tome and Principe Saudi Arabia Senegal Serbia Seychelles Sierra Leone Singapore Slovakia Slovenia Solomon Islands Somalia South Africa South Georgia and the South Sandwich Islands Spain Sri Lanka Sudan Suriname Svalbard and Jan Mayen Swaziland Sweden Switzerland Syrian Arab Republic Taiwan Tajikistan Tanzania, United Republic of Thailand Timor-Leste Togo Tokelau Tonga Trinidad and Tobago Tunisia Turkey Turkmenistan Turks and Caicos Islands Tuvalu Uganda Ukraine United Arab Emirates United Kingdom United States United States Minor Outlying Islands Uruguay Uzbekistan Vanuatu Venezuela Vietnam Virgin Islands, British Virgin Islands, U.S. Wallis and Futuna Western Sahara Yemen Zambia Zimbabwe

ZIP/Postal Code: 

Check the following boxes to state that:
----------------------------------------

Each box below must be checked \*

 UNDER PENALTY OF PERJURY, you are the owner or an agent authorized to act on behalf of the owner of an exclusive right that is allegedly infringed.

 You have a good faith belief that the use of the content in the manner complained of, is not authorized by the copyright owner, its agent, or the law.

 The information in this notification is accurate.

 You acknowledge that you may be subject to liability if you knowingly make a material misrepresentation that activity is infringing. Fair use should also be taken into consideration.

 You acknowledge that abuse of this tool may result in termination of your account.

Please Note:
------------

The copyright owner’s name will be published on Youporn in place of the disabled content. This will become part of the public record of your request, along with your description of the work(s) allegedly infringed. All the information provided in this DMCA Takedown Form (including your personal information) are part of the full takedown notice and may be forwarded to the uploader of the allegedly infringing content. By submitting this form you consent to having your information revealed in this way.

We reserve the right to challenge abuses of the DMCA process, and your use of this form does not waive that right.

Type Your Full Name Here To Provide Your Electronic Signature:
--------------------------------------------------------------

Electronic Signature: 

Submit

#### Success!

Your DMCA takedown request has been sent successfully.

Close

#### Error

An error happened while submitting your request. Please try again later or contact customer support. Thank you.

Close

#### Error

In order to submit this form you must disable AdBlock.

Close

EU Digital Services Act
=======================

As of July 31, 2024, Youporn has 3,834,315 average monthly recipients of the service in the European Union, calculated as an average over the period of the past six months.

For inquiries and requests and complaints related to the Digital Services Act, please contact us at [dsa@youporn.com](mailto:dsa@youporn.com). If your request is not related to the Digital Services Act, please do not use this email address to communicate with us but rather:

* For general inquiries use [support@youporn.com](mailto:support@youporn.com) or visit our [Support page at Youporn](https://www.youporn.com/information/#support) for further information.
* For messages relating to your data and privacy inquiries, use [privacy@youporn.com](mailto:privacy@youporn.com) or visit our [privacy notice at Youporn](https://www.youporn.com/information/#privacy) for further information.

Recommendations and tailoring content to you at Youporn
=======================================================

Who and what our recommendations are for and why we do it

At Youporn, your user experience is important to us.

Given the nature of our services, this means we want to get tailored content, like videos, photos, and GIFs, to you while respecting your privacy, safety, and the laws and regulations in your jurisdiction. To do this, we’ve developed methods that give you what you want while keeping you safe and within the legal parameters of where you live. If you want safety and privacy specifics, check out our [Terms of Service](https://www.youporn.com/information/#terms), [Trust & Safety](https://help.pornhub.com/hc/en-us/categories/4419836212499) policy, [Privacy Notice](https://www.youporn.com/information/#privacy), and [EU DSA](https://www.youporn.com/information/#eudsa) pages.

Here’s a look at how we deliver a top-notch user experience to you:

How we recommend relevant content and ads

To deliver content and ads that suit your preferences, we offer different recommendation options for you to explore:

* **Hot, hottest, and featured videos**
    
    On our homepage and in the **Hottest** section, you can browse the hottest porn. These videos are featured by an algorithm for their high quality.
    
    To feature videos, we consider per country, the video’s views, ratings, comments, favorite markings, and total time watched.
    
    To sort these featured videos, we use the same factors as above, together with the time we featured the video. You can also sort chronologically by the time we featured the videos by selecting _Featured Recently_, where applicable.
    
    Hot, hottest, and featured videos may differ by country. On the **Hottest** page, you can switch countries in the _Country_ drop-down menu.
    
* **Recommended**
    
    We provide videos that could be interesting for you on a dedicated page.
    
    Our recommendations are based on metadata of the videos you watched, how you interacted with these videos, and popular videos in your region based on views, ratings, comments, favoriting, and total time watched.
    
    You can sort chronologically by most recent recommendations, as well as by relevance to you, which we determine based on the factors described above.
    
    If you prefer non-personalized recommendations, we offer these as hot videos on the help page, as described above.
    
* **Related content**
    
    On the video and GIF pages, we show related content. To determine the content you may find most relevant, we consider the metadata of the videos you watched, how you interacted with these videos, and popular videos in your region based on views, ratings, comments, favorite markings, and total time watched.
    
* **Random**
    
    Let us surprise you. We provide content that we selected randomly.
    
* **Trending searches**
    
    We display trending searches based on the frequency of recent searches by other users in the same country as you.
    
* **TrafficJunky ads**
    
    Where we deliver dynamic advertising, we use the following factors to identify advertisements that we believe may be most relevant to you:
    
    * Geographic location
    * Date and time
    * Context the ad is placed in
    * Demographics
    * Previous interactions with ads or content
    * Operating system
    * Browser settings (model, version, and language)
    * Internet connection, that is, IP range, internet service provider, connection type, and region.
    
    If you deactivate _Targeting/Advertising Cookies_, we do not use demographics or previous interactions with ads or content to find the most relevant advertising for you.
    
    _Targeting/Advertising Cookies_ can be switched off at any time by going to the footer of the website and choosing **Manage Cookies**.

How the sorting of content works

We want to make sure that you always see the content that you enjoy most. To enhance your user experience, we provide a variety of sorting options for you to choose from.

Where available, you can switch options in the upper right corner. Sorting can be based on how we recommend relevant content and on the following options, where applicable:

* **Homepage sorting:** Content on the homepage is sorted based on the collective behavior of users to show videos that were watched and enjoyed. We also account for if you liked or watched a video, and what’s the hottest and trending content. If you don't want recommendations based on your viewed content, you can turn _Personalized Recommendations_ off on the hamburger menu.
* **Most recent and newest:** Content is sorted by publication date.
* **Most viewed:** Content is sorted by number of views. Where applicable, you can customize the relevant time frame and country for the views.
* **Top rated:** Content is sorted by the number of likes and dislikes. Where applicable, you can customize the relevant time frame for the ratings.
* **Longest:** Videos are sorted by length.
* **A-Z or alphabetical:** Content is sorted by name or title.
* **Most subscribed:** Content is sorted by number of subscriptions.
* **Number of videos:** Content is sorted by number of attributable videos.
* **Most popular:**
    * **Categories and Channels:** Content is sorted by number of views. Where applicable, you can customize the relevant time frame and country for the views.
    * **Pornstars, Models, and Community:** To determine the most popular content creators, we consider views, the number of times the pornstar or model is searched, and subscriptions.
* **Top trending or trending:**
    * **Pornstars and Models:** To determine the top trending content creators, we consider the popularity of a creator’s content within a specific time period.
* **Most relevant:** Most relevant content is shown based on keyword search results, such as matching tags, model and pornstar names, titles of content, and categories to the search entry. We also show newer content first, specifically content with more engagement.

More options on how you can customize our recommendations

On the homepage for Youporn, select the **User** icon, and you can turn on or off _Personalized Recommendations_. If you turn off this feature, the videos you watched and how you interacted with these videos don’t influence any content recommendations we show you.

 HELP & SUPPORT

 WORK WITH US

 CONNECT WITH US

 TRUST & SAFETY

© Youporn 2006 - 2024
